I'm gonna find the demon eye now.
Because we have demon business.
Where is it?
Exactly.
I promise I'll double check the map from now on, no matter what.
Okay, so it's right next to the tree.
No more map.
Back in the game.
There.
I can't believe this has happened twice in this stream and I have never had that happen before.
Maybe once in tunic.
I think I did that by accident.
But never here.
Today is the first day that I'm messing up like that.
Okay, so this is the plan.
Ooh, there it is!
There it fucking is!
Okay, you.
We're gonna put you in a... in a spot.
Nobody will ever get to you.
Have fun down there.
What's up?
Okay, I have multiple places.
I want to try this eye, by the way.
Oh, can I even... Yes, I can.
Can I?
No.
I need my thingy.
Laser cutter.
I could just make a hole through.
Yeah, why not?
I'm proficient with this thing by now.
I've made so many holes.
Maybe I should have just gone up here and made the hole up there.
Doesn't matter, I'm committed.
I'm committed.
I have officially cut down the world tree.
Not taking that.
I can tell you that much.
Man, it feels good to be home.
You know, back in the beginning.
Cheers, everybody.
This game is a blast.
Oh, wait a minute.
No, keep going.
Yeah.
So, now the plan is the following.
Listen.
I have the demon eye.
I shall be going to all the demon eye places.
And...
But on the way, I'm gonna look for more hearts because we're gonna get the extra health.
Perk that I left behind.
And we're gonna get the last perk because we have 21,000 buckaroos in our banger count.
Okay?
That's the plan.
Why does my... Why does this do no damage?
I don't understand.
It says three damage drill, but it does nothing to enemies.
I don't get it.
That's a weird system there.
Also, we can find some blood in here.
Yep.
Like that.
Blow up the entire hemisphere.
Weirdly, this is faster than traversing the hemisphere.
This is the realest dig ever.
And they're the roots of the tree.
So, I've already been in here.
But there is actually health in there, I could take.
Should I do that?
No, not yet.
That would be stupid when I can heal with blood.
What's happened here?
Is that a worm?
Oh, it is.
It looked so straight that I was like, that can't be a worm.
Oh, it broke this.
Wait, how do I pick... I can't pick up teleportation without teleporting, though.
Fuck.
I gotta find an actual flask of it, I guess.
I mean, I guess I could, but it would take forever and I would be teleporting everywhere and it'd be a mess.
So, a real question for you guys.
How come when the flask touches the teleportation, that the flask doesn't get teleported?
Hm?
Or when the teleportation touches other teleportation molecules?
How come that doesn't teleport it everywhere?
That's what I wonder.
Okay.
Drink.
Drink the blood!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Nah, there's nothing here.
I think I did explore most of this place anyway, so...
I think it's time to leave.
Next!
Oh,
we got more of these.
Huh.
They're actually nice to have.
I'll take one more.
Thank you.
Sparkly bounce, double scatter, concentrated light.
All kinds of spells.
Right.
Let's make a hole.
Lovely.
The coal pits.
Meow.
This is the ultimate digging level.
This is where you want to go if you want to dig.
Like, anything can be dug through here.
There's like nothing that can't be dug through.
Or almost nothing.
Oh, dude!
Fungal caverns!
It's fungal caverns time.
I kind of want to find some blood first.
That's too much lava for me.
Way too much.
Aha!
There's a corpse there.
Cool.
There's got to be a big pile of blood here somewhere.
I believe I made big piles of blood.
Or maybe I didn't.
I mean, we have 330 HP.
This better fucking work, by the way.
I am 73% sure this is going to work.
That's polymorphine.
Ew.
What's that?
Gunpowder?
I'm looking for... I'm looking for teleportation potions.
Toxic rock.
Where was this place?
Somewhere over here, I want to say.
Look how empty this place is.
I cleaned up here.
Okay, there's nothing up there.
Oh, here it is.
Here it is.
Yeah, look at this.
Okay, here we go.
It's a mushroom man with three eyes.
Maybe I just wait.
Fuck yeah, dude!
Okay, it's time to read the book again.
I'm so stoked this is actually working.
They felt our understanding of this world was to be forbidden.
They hit something here in this room, but I like the ability to truly see what is here.
I wonder if I need to get high, you know?
The shroom is a sign.
It's like a sign from the gods.
Thou need to get high on these shrooms to enter my secret palace.
Something like that.
Hold on.
Let's do it.
Let's get high.
We're getting maximally high right now.
Especially because we're in a safe region here, sort of.
There's no enemies.
Is this enough?
I'm tripping balls.
Maybe I hold this?
Wait, what?
Nothing's happening.
Maybe I'm resistant to getting high.
Maybe I have done something.
Hmm.
Okay, that's very interesting.
They hit something here in this room.
Okay.
That's odd.
I'm not quite sure.
Let's think on that.
Whiskey.
Can I find teleportation, please?
Or unstable.
I just need it in the flask.
Then I'm happy.
Acceleration.
I may just take that instead of... I mean...
Why not, right?
Diggity-dig?
Oh wait, I'm already at 47% satiated, so I'm just going to drink some of it.
There we go.
Levitation.
Why am I not getting high, though?
I don't understand.
Did I not... enough?
Hold on, I'm going to eat some more.
Oh wait, I'm poisoned!
Yeah, maybe let's try getting high somewhere else.
And not next to that book.
Maybe it doesn't work there.
Dude, I'm definitely tripping balls.
My screen is not even changing.
Oh, I ate too much as well.
Overeating.
God damn it.
Alright.
That's odd.
Why is that?
I don't understand.
I don't get it.
Hmm.
It's got to be related to the fact that I have the demon eye, right?
Like, what else could it be?
Okay, I need to find a couple hearts real quick.
I can go so quickly through the level.
Let's go to all the places I didn't explore.
If there's even any left.
Like here.
It's a little bit dark.
Oops.
I am low on HP as well here.
Where are the massive blood pools I made?
Or is that in the next level?
Maybe.
Meow.
It's wild.
Okay,
that's water.
You know what?
Fuck it.
There's nothing here.
Go!
Next!
Okay, I could heal.
I'm not gonna.
I'm really squeezing the lemon here.
I know.
I'm a lemon squeezer.
What can I say?
The snowy depths.
This one.
Yeah, I know you're angry.
But you know what?
I don't care!
Oh wait, you're not angry.
You look the other way.
That's right.
Okay, I'm still clumsy.
I need to walk it off.
Oh, hello there.
Instantly died.
To the prowess of my fire power.
This is where I last died, by the way.
Because I dug into a watery thingy.
With an Ukuskivi inside.
So I need to be super careful about that.
I need to go slow.
I've learned my lesson.
Okay, here we go.
Blood.
Oh, it's all meat!
Fuck yeah!
Hold on, I need to...
I need to pee.
Get it out.
Empty my potion.
Now I'm tripping!
That's so interesting.
Very weird.
I guess there's something about that region.
After I revealed the big mushroom, maybe I'm just unable to get high in that region.
I don't know why that would be, though.
Don't eat the rotten meat.
Make blood out of the rotten meat.
Yes, yes!
A little vampire lifestyle here.
We also got some blood down here.
Oh, also some water.
Don't overeat.
Shit, I overate.
Is that...
Oh, all the blood!
Fuck me.
Why didn't I just look down a little bit?
Well, that's nice, though.
Give me blood.
Okay, don't drown.
Although that would be a wonderful death for a vampire as me.
Drinking what I loved while dying.
I'm still clumsy.
Nice.
Full HP, man.
Get a full bottle.
Let's move.
Okay.
There's gotta be something I missed here.
There's just gotta be.
This is my favorite track in the game.
So far.
I think closely followed by the track in the sand caves.
That's all frozen.
Oh, man.
I overate so much.
Look at that.
125%.
I'm so slow.
Oh, I know what to do.
I know what to do.
I know where there's a heart.
I almost forgot about this.
Watch me find it so quick.
Wait, why is there growth here?
An empty potion as well.
Was that me?
Did I put that there?
I maybe did.
It's hard to say.
Man, it's hard to be a wizard when you've drank so much.
Wait, this is actually gonna be hard without...
No, it's not gonna be hard.
It's gonna be fine.
Shit, is it?
Is it though?
Is it gonna be fine?
Would love some teleport.
Shit.
Up here.
And at some point, I'm gonna fly to the other side.
Come on, do I have any...
Yeah, I do actually have some lift with that.
What about this one?
No lift with that one.
What about my laser cutter?
Do I have lift with that?
I'm kidding, I'm not gonna try that.
Let's go.
Oh, easy, easy.
Easy.
Easy...
No, I don't hear it.
Oh, here we go.
When the sound is at its maximum.
I think here.
Oh, wait, shit, shit, shit.
Oh, look how close I am!
Fuck, that was on the nose!
I'm sick!
What does this say?
Heat my warning or death and decay will follow.
Wait a minute, I'm just noticing something.
Is it telling me death and decay will follow if I take this heart?
Is that the implication here?
I don't care about death!
Yoink!
Mine, bitch.
Heal up, and then we go.
Oh, yeah.
So now the plan is, we're gonna go...
I think I've explored most of this area.
But I'm just gonna give it a quick ones over here.
Like these dark regions, like this.
Just be careful of water pockets.
Like that.
I don't see electricity.
Should be okay.
And also explore these mountains of snow.
Sometimes there's hearts in there.
Mountains of snow.
Nothing exciting so far.
I love doing that.
Blow it all up!
So, do you think I'll ever find a teleport in this run?
Or is it like a...
You're not allowed to teleport in this run.
Because it feels that way.
It feels like I'm just not allowed.
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh.
That was a bomb.
Okay, we've got dark areas.
Right!
Circle of...
You know what?
Let me try that again.
Circle of buoyancy.
We can get rid of...
I don't know what to get rid of.
Maybe that one.
A field of levitative magic.
Okay.
Ooh, hello there.
Not today.
Look at this!
I haven't been here.
Levitation?
Double wants.
Okay.
Critical on...
Burning!
Not terrible, I guess.
If you put a burning modifier on...
One of your spells, I just don't have that.
At least not on me, and maybe I have some somewhere.
Nothing in there.
Like, the whole critical modifier on something...
I think is actually kind of insane.
And the reason I say that is, if you can somehow guarantee that...
The something that is the critical on is always applied...
You're essentially doing five times normal damage.
Like, constantly.
And that seems big.
That seems really crazy.
If you can make something nice with that.
Oh yeah, the wand!
Heavy spread.
With fireball orbit.
Oh yeah.
Like, I didn't last long.
Aha!
A wand?
Spark bolts.
Water potion.
Now, I kind of just want to try and dig left now.
Acid potion...
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Let me go in here again.
Maybe the demon eye can be used for something in here.
Probably not, but...
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Did I leave it?
Ha!
Thanks!
And this said what?
As with everything else, every celestial body has its counterpart.
Right, hold on.
I'm going to take a picture.
I need to take pictures of all of these.
And then I compile them in the end.
To a big story.
And then we try to make sense of it.
Yeah.
So, I've been here.
All that is done.
Lovely.
Let's go.
Whoo!
Be careful.
These guys...
are still just hanging out in there.
So, the Paasilma is not going to gain access, right?
It's not going to actually.
But I could just do this.
I just want to murder them, basically.
There we go.
Ping pong path.
That could be nice with this.
Right?
Kind of want to do it.
I'm going to grab it and come back for the other wand.
That's gunpowder.
Let's go up and change it.
Dig.
I need to remember exactly where my wand was.
So, I almost went straight up from where I was.
I reached this point.
From this point straight down.
Totally keep moving.
Oh.
Hold on.
Whoa!
Hello!
Whoops.
Oh my god.
That's what I'm talking about, baby!
Oh, I thought it was a teleport.
What's that?
Transmuse various liquids and powdery substances within a projectile's range into something else.
And it's chaotic?
Hmmm.
No.
Nope.
And it's also not a spell.
It's on the wand itself.
If it was on... If it was a spell, maybe I would have checked it out.
Here we are.
So, I just need to confirm as well here.
That this ping pong path or whatever...
Oh, man.
What should I... You know what?
Get rid of this one.
Giant fire bolts?
No.
Nope.
So, this one...
Is that going to work with my...
Hmmm.
Healing.
Deadly healing.
Oh.
Hold on.
I need to get up and left.
But the thing is, I still don't have friendly fire on it.
So, I need to apply something that will actually make it damage me, like bloodlust.
Ah, go here.
And then when we're here, we go down.
Brrr.
Whipsidoos.
Gun... Ah, it's right here.
Yes.
Nice.
Got it.
Nothing there.
Is it time?
We leave.
Okay.
And now we're in this spot.
Wait, where am I right now?
Easy base.
I basically want to go through this quick, I think, because it's kind of impossible to know where I've been.
Maybe you want to go to the very western edge of this place, just because I don't think I've been there.
I've definitely been here.
Here's the bar!
Levitation and whiskey.
None of them might want that.
Heat me up.
And I've been here as well.
Okay, so this is the edge.
Yeah, I was here.
Oh yeah!
Nice refill there.
Let's go!
Okay, hold on, I need to check my notes.
What else did I have on my list?
Email and fungal caverns.
Right.
That's it.
Okay, perfect.
Just need to double check.
And I have removed the overlay.
Check.
Let's go.
Liquid detonation.
That one was intriguing.
Converts nearby non-magical liquids into explosive gunpowder.
I think that sounds amazing.
I love that.
I love it.
But maybe I...
I just keep it on me.
For now.
What was that?
Giant explosion.
Oh, this is a limited item as well.
The magic arrow with trigger.
I actually want that.
I'm gonna throw this away.
Give me one of these.
Because I need to experiment.
With how better that is if I replace the spark bolt.
That costs 10 mana, right?
This costs 35.
So it's a lot more expensive.
And we do run Oom with that.
But if we find an add mana, maybe this will substantially increase damage.
For now, put it there.
Standard setup.
Okay, on we go.
Just explore a little bit more here.
Just the dark areas.
I may just go through.
Is this the one where I didn't take the perk?
It is not, wow.
Man, I have all kinds of crazy spells lying around.
This is the one where I didn't go through.
I mean, I did go through and I didn't take the spell.
I also don't think I explored all of this place.
But a lot of it I did.
Unfortunately, I cannot dig freely here.
There's a lot of metal.
Oh, you're alive.
Look at this fucking menagerie of enemies.
Guarding the portal.
Ha ha, bounced off.
Fuck you, man.
I'm not done in this place, though.
Oh, look at the blood.
Oh, man.
This is a massacre.
It really is.
Oh, no, the blood is burning.
Somehow.
That sucks.
My health is 777.
That is the luckiest amount of health ever.
Come on.
Ah, what?
Okay.
Let's see what else we have.
We just gotta squeeze the line a little bit more before we get that hurt.
Just explore the rest of this place, you know?
Get that little extra HP.
I thought that was a laser beam, but it's just blood.
Oh, I can actually get through those pipes with my digging.
Makes it a bit easier.
Piano lookout for electricity.
Ooh, what do we got there?
Look at that.
Got a little shop.
Black hole and slithering pad.
Ooh, they cost a lot.
5,000?
No way.
I need to save that for perk re-rolls.
Hell, yeah.
Man, that guy is dropping a lot of oil.
Oh, I'm slippery.
Like I'm ice skating.
Those guys are annoying.
Oh, that's another one of those shield bros.
Gonna come up here?
Kinda want a big left here.
But, I'm gonna go grab that perk before I do.
I don't wanna go nuts.
I need to grab that perk, right?
I've been saying this for literally 10 hours.
At some point, I need to stop.
Oh, the slowdown!
Whoa, the game is like...
Something big just happened somewhere in the game.
And my CPU was having trouble.
It was like slow motion.
Oh.
That is the luki layer.
We're not going in there again.
Did I check that one?
I did.
We've been through most of these places.
I think it's time to move on.
What?
Oh.
I was poisoned.
Let's go.
It's time.
Wait a minute.
How am I at 784 HP?
Was my max HP 777?
No, maybe it wasn't.
Alright, here it is!
It's happening!
It paid off waiting with it, guys.
1176.
I'm going to take a victory bite out of my sandwich here.
I don't want any of those.
It's time to dig.
Whoa!
I can feel the HP increase.
It's quite substantial.
My wand is underpowered.
We need to make it even stronger.
Temple of the art, that's right.
I keep saying the art.
But it's temple of the art.
Wait.
Doesn't that look like a small passilma?
It's either a black hole or a small passilma.
Three of them.
Whoops.
Bam!
Just evade.
Wait, save.
So tanky.
Okay, so this is the place with the triangle.
Oh, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
Kind of want to do that again.
And you know what, last time I used black holes and it was super effective.
I may just do the same.
Freezing liquid.
Nah.
I don't think I want that.
Oh, this is really dense.
Look at that.
Even my laser cutter has trouble getting through it.
What is that even?
It's just brickwork.
Oh, I forget what each of the colors do.
I think purple is the one that tins everything toxic.
Release the hemises.
Okay, my wand is actually decent still.
It's just not an instant kill, you know.
I'm getting a little spoiled here, okay?
I get it.
Oh, look at that!
I see something.
Oh, we got to get rid of this guy first.
Oh my God, I get in there effectively.
Probably just make a...
So there's definitely some kind of liquid that needs to go in here.
Wait, do we put fire in there?
To blow up the gunpowder, which will then remove this rock and gain access?
That is something that would make sense to me.
Okay, sleep...
He's scared of me here.
Let's just...
Man, why is he moving towards that place?
Stop it!
Alright, fine.
Go!
Is he gonna rock into me?
He is, fuck you.
Fuck you!
Yeah, I hate you!
Quick!
Quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick!
Worth it.
Totally worth it.
Even my laser cutter is underpowered in this place.
Part of me wants to just go to the perks and see what there is.
While I still have 24k, you know?
Because that perk could save my life in here.
Whatever that perk may be.
Oh, I'm getting so much money.
I'm gonna be re-rolling for ages.
Oh man, what's that?
That could have been scary, man.
What if that was polymorphism?
Did he just bleed acid?
Or like toxic sludge?
What is with your HP?
The red one collapses things.
There we go.
The thing I'm really scared about here is shooting some of these mages from a distance.
And he teleports me to where he was and I'm in the middle of some shit, you know?
That attack does so much damage.
If I get hit by it.
What the
fuck is that?
Someone in there.
He's charmed!
Oh, it's a horta.
Why couldn't it have been a friendly?
A heezy bro.
So far, so good.
Still haven't found a big collection of blood here.
Right when I say that.
We get some.
Ow!
Thought you were dead!
You gonna follow me around everywhere?
Oh no, it's these guys.
Just don't attack them.
Just ignore them, really.
Holy shit!
Oh, fuck me.
That's getting a little too risky here.
Fuck off!
Further down.
I mean, I could easily win right now, I think.
Just going for the end boss, but I'm not gonna.
Why would you ever do that?
After the first win?
What is the point?
I guess to get that counter up.
Actually, that's... I can see that.
Now, the green one.
I think that's... the green one is the one that produces a big explosion, right?
Yes.
No!
That's the toxic... Oh, fuck.
Dang it.
No, cursed.
I keep mixing up those two.
Cursed and toxic.
It's different.
Cursed is the one that damages you even when you're right next to it.
All that looks... not good.
Wait, does that polymorph?
I heard the polymorph sound effect.
That would be really scary.
Shit, I'm stuck.
Wait, that was pretty sick.
Alright, let's get it.
Let's see the perks.
This is exciting.
Do we get a teleport here at the end?
What?
Hey!
The one I need!
Oh my god.
That's amazing.
I think I'm gonna reload this one.
Not reload.
What's it called?
Refresh.
Oh!
Man, I gotta take it, right?
I gotta take it.
I do have a lot of money.
Oh, but I don't.
This is the last re-roll I have.
Oh, I'm not gonna do it.
I'm gonna take it.
Don't be dumb.
We need explosion immunity, man.
We gotta do it.
Okay.
You can't go wrong with explosion immunity.
Bloodlust!
Do I even have money?
I do.
I have 23k, so I can buy a bunch of these once.
And look at that.
Energy orb with a trigger.
Man.
50 mana drain?
Holy crap!
Jesus!
That's way too much.
Replace that one.
Makes a projectile fly back and forth.
A projectile flies in a spiraling pattern.
Oh, it even adds three damage.
Okay.
Um...
Wait.
Oh, but it's also able to hurt you.
Yeah.
Okay, so the only question I have now, though, is because this one does 30 damage, right?
If I add bloodlust to it, that's another 33.
So, in total, that's 63 damage I will do to myself.
But, how much is the healing?
That's the question, right?
If that's lower than that, it's bad.
So, let's see.
Let's put all these down here.
Hopefully it's enough.
Did it work?
Wait, 966?
Oh, it's totally... Wow!
Did you see the healing on that?
Holy shit, guys.
I've made it big.
We are back.
Holy fucking shit.
That is an insane healing.
Wow.
Very nice.
Now, can I make it more consistent so I don't need water?
Um...
Maybe like this?
So, watch this now.
I need to find a method to do this to myself without being in the water.
Oh.
Wait.
Okay.
So, I need a bit of horizontal distance.
If you're fast, you can definitely...
Yep.
Oh, that's amazing.
Can we make it even better?
Spiral.
I think I tried this, but I only tried it in water.
Ah, yeah, it doesn't come back to me.
I need the boomerang spell, whatever it's called.
That would be the one, right?
That one totally works.
That is the one.
The only thing we gotta be careful with here is that...
Oh, hold on a second.
I wonder if my...
Oh, never mind.
I thought I had a crit perk, but I don't.
That must have been the last run.
Anyway, I was wondering whether or not if I accidentally crit myself with this.
If that would do like five times the amount on myself as well.
Ooh.
Would have been bad, right?
But I don't have that here, so that's totally fine.
Alright, these are my final perks.
Can't get any more.
I think it's a good selection of perks.
Extra health, explosion, fire, peace with the gods is amazing.
And the extra perks have made sure that I've probably gotten some good ones.
Right?
Very nice.
Okay, throw this away.
And let's get another one instead.
Hold on, what is this?
Venomous curse.
I...
I think I never tried this.
I got it once, but I never tried it.
Let's get it.
And what else?
Holy lands.
120 mana drain.
Does 30 damage.
Wait, damage holy.
It has a holy damage modifier.
That is actually quite interesting, isn't it?
Is this able to damage me?
Fast flying, penetrating lands.
Wait, fast flying?
Is this a joke?
The fuck you mean?
Eh?
Now the question is, I can't take explosion damage, but this is holy.
So I wonder if this will damage me if I'm too close.
Let's see.
I block it.
Hey!
Okay, perfect.
Nice.
Good to know.
So I guess the explosion damage is...
a damage type in itself.
But the holy lands impact is doing...
holy damage.
Yeah.
Oh, I also have this one, remember.
I have circle of vigor as well.
I completely forgot about that.
I have healing, guys.
Forever now.
That is insane.
I just need to figure out a way to...
stack mult... Oh, I guess I can...
I was about to say, if I put multiple healings...
Also, where are my healings?
I need this back.
Hold on, put this up here.
Give me that.
Where are my healing things?
Is it over here?
It must be.
Replace... Hold on.
Well, put it here for now.
.03.
All of these can sort of go...
This is actually a nice one to store spells on.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
It always casts something.
Causes a projectile to aim straight upwards a short time after.
Oh, hold on a second.
Wait, I have an even better idea now.
We can make this really nice, so we don't need horizontal.
We also need... Oh, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude.
This is it.
Quadruple spell.
I think I want to keep that one.
Maybe we'll get rid of this one.
It kind of sucks.
Circle of... Do I want that?
Yeah.
No.
I mean, if I had Tinker with Wands everywhere, I would take it, because then I could try things on the fly while I'm out and about.
But now that I don't have it, it's actually what's going...
My experimentation is going to be limited, because I don't want to go out and go back every time I try something new.
It would be horrible.
Absolutely horrible.
Anyway, my plan is this.
Put that there.
And that's it.
Oh, wait, I need something to damage myself, of course.
Shit, I can only have one of these at a time, though.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, guys, guys, guys!
I know what to do!
Look at it!
Can we stack it?
Wait.
Can I make- can I copy a random spell and that spell is three spells?
On a heal?
Oh, but wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
We're gonna do massive damage on ourselves.
Didn't think about that.
Bad idea, bad idea, bad idea.
Abort, abort.
But we can use it on circle of vigor.
Circle of vigor.
Doo doo doo doo doo doo.
So I guess I'll just keep one of them on me for now.
And then I have to hot swap them whenever I need more.
But the problem is, this is no longer a storage wand, because I can't really...
Yeah, I'm gonna throw away stuff that I...
Fuck.
Throw away the homing.
Because we're not gonna get unlimited spells anymore, so that doesn't matter.
Throw away that one.
Throw away...
What else?
I think we're okay there.
Put this up here.
Put this there.
Maybe throw away the digging blast, because I already have some.
I feel like these are important.
This one is kind of shit.
Let's leave it here.
Put this up there.
Ping pong path, I want to keep...
that one.
Okay.
Nice.
Maybe I can put some spells down here.
Because why not?
I
mean, if I do that, it's just gonna... it doesn't change anything, really.
It doesn't cost mana, I guess, but... is it a big deal?
Let's see.
No, it's fine.
Freeze up a slot, at least.
Venomous curse.
How much does that cost?
30 mana drain?
Shit.
I wonder if there are some bosses that take damage when they heal, if that makes sense.
So if I hit them with this, they're just gonna insta-die.
That would be a cool mechanic.
You know?
Oh, I never tried this, actually.
Let's try it.
Oh, shit.
No, wait, this had a short amount of time.
Oh, no, it doesn't work as I intended.
Shit.
Okay, I thought it was like instant, almost.
Well, dang it.
I guess...
Well, shit.
This wand is not gonna be used, then.
Hold on.
Is this there?
There.
Replace this wand now.
With, I guess...
That's fine, I guess.
Maybe a little bigger wand would be nice.
Oh, that's a nice storage wand.
I kinda want this one, by the way.
I want that.
Critical and bloody enemies.
I want this one too.
It costs hero mana drain!
How is this not just a win?
Amazing.
Causes a projectile to aim straight downwards.
You know, that...
is actually...
not bad.
Maybe that's what I have to do here.
Maybe that's even better.
We gotta try it.
How much of a short time?
Okay.
I guess quite a bit.
This is more safe.
I feel like the ping pong path is the way to go.
That is the one I can replicate.
More easily.
And I don't need a ton of vertical space for that to happen.
This one...
We're gonna... Hold on.
Let's see the difference if there even is any.
Okay.
Now we put this in here.
Oh!
Whoa!
It is...
way faster!
Oh shit!
Hold on.
Yeah, we need this one though.
We need it.
Unless we don't...
Hold up.
Whoo!
Wait a minute...
Is that better?
That's kind of impossible to tell because this one is not gonna take damage.
Fuck's sake.
That's even faster, isn't it?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Put this one back.
Is there a difference?
Oh, you know what?
One way to test if I'm shooting faster is how much recoil I have.
Okay, so I go like that and with it on...
The same.
But look at this now.
Oh, it runs out so fast though.
Man, I need add mana.
I gotta find a one with that.
I really need that.
For now, this is okay.
This is okay.
I may put this on.
No, it costs too much mana.
Alright.
Cool.
I think we're good to go.
Rock and roll time.
This is my setup.
Yep.
Very cool.
Now we dig up.
It's digging time.
Yep, you're angry, I know.
Now we go to the ancient laboratory.
And then after that, assuming I survive, we're gonna go to the wizard's den.
And explore more there.
Maybe even the meat realm.
Although that place seems a little nuts.
And I feel like my wand may be a little underpowered for that.
That place seems like the enemies do insane damage.
Compared to... why is it so far up here?
This is way farther up than the others, by the way.
Alright.
I made it.
I'm just gonna go straight up, basically.
Unless I find stuff on the way like this, of course.
What's that?
Projectile area teleport.
If a valid target appears somewhere in the proximity of a projectile, the projectile will teleport right on top of the target?
Say what?
That sounds really cool.
How much of a proximity though?
Oh, it does cost 60 mana.
This is not something we can utilize.
We need add mana for that sort of stuff.
We just don't have the means.
Oh, this place.
I don't know if I should try this.
That thing was scary last time.
Nah, fuck it.
I'm not doing it.
I'm going up.
I have a date.
With a certain someone.
What's that?
Goddammit.
Oh, it's an egg.
How conveniently placed?
Whoop.
I feel like my one is worse than before.
Did I fuck it up somehow?
Okay.
I'm digging.
The danger here is that there's lava up there or something when I can't see, and you should probably take a look first.
Wait, where am I going?
Oh, am I already digging up to the next level?
It's possible that I'm doing that.
Oh yeah, I think so.
By the way, I don't think I've damaged myself a single time using this...
weapon here.
Isn't that impressive?
That's got to be a new record for me.
I swear to God, I did not do that on purpose.
Fuck me.
What a timing on that.
I was trying to aim for this little spot here and somehow I hit myself.
What?
Fuck off, man.
The timing on that.
I got to say, though, I feel like me saying that out loud may have contributed to it somehow.
Maybe deep in my subconscious I got a little laid back.
You know, like... I don't know.
I'm going to take this.
Thanks.
That was kind of funny, though.
Okay, we got to test this.
This is the field test.
Let's see if it works in the field.
I need to run before I shoot.
Go.
Hey, the field test.
Successful.
We don't fucking need blood anymore.
We've got infinite healing pretty much.
With all... I mean, we have so many spell refreshers and there's so many healing bolts we have.
Oh, it's practically unlimited.
What's that?
Concentrated mana.
Make a way in here.
No, you know what?
Yeah, just no.
No, go in here.
These sort of fire thingies remind me of Blade Runner.
You know, one of the like the opening shots of the city.
Something about it.
Wow, you are not dead.
Also, I'm explosion immune.
I have to remember.
So I could technically go a little nuts with my wands now.
Make something explodey.
Whoa!
They're just hanging out there.
What the hell?
Awesome.
Okay, here we are.
Okay, it's time to dig.
Go.
Stay mad.
All right, we're in the jungle.
Okay, so let's think about this fight now.
He has a shield.
And he shoots a shit ton of spells at you.
And you got to dodge those.
Oh, but wait, I don't have teleport.
How the fuck am I going to dodge that shit?
Oh, no, I'm going to fucking die.
I don't even do that much damage.
Like, my damage is nothing to write home about.
Shit.
I'm scared, guys.
I feel like I need to bring out bigger guns.
Maybe I'll try to make something out of the...
Holy lands.
That seems kind of dope.
You know, put some speed up on it and stuff?
Seems like it would be kind of cool.
Can we do something like that?
It costs 120 mana.
Holy shit.
Nobody has money for that.
Or mana, I mean.
Uh...
Okay.
Yeah, I don't know, man.
I guess we just got to try.
Also, while I'm here, just replace this with a full one.
And let's dig up.
Let's cycle.
Oh, we're going to be draining blood here.
Oh, that's a lot.
That's a lot of blood.
That holy mountain is going to be full of blood.
Am I at the entrance already?
Oh, hold on.
The entrance should be here.
Perfect.
Hey, some black holes.
Uh...
Should I take those?
No.
What the fuck?
Look at this!
Wait, did I do that?
Sure...
What?
I did not do that.
It wasn't me.
Did I?
No, this is a...
What a weird way to dig.
Oh, look at all that blood.
I'm drinking.
I may as well drink this.
Oh, lovely, lovely.
Oh, wait, I'm actually going to drown in the blood.
Not a good way to go.
A bit more...
Oh, wait, lava, lava, lava, lava, lava, lava, lava, lava.
Let's circumvent that.
Beautiful.
From here I could technically get back using...
the right hand...
I'm actually going to do that.
I'm going on the right side.
We're taking the shortcut.
I hear someone.
Anything exciting over here?
Nope.
Okay, so we're almost there.
Now we just need to climb up.
Heh heh.
Ah, can I make it?
Eh.
Ah, shit!
Let's go.
I don't have enough recoil yet to do something like that.
A tablet!
Actually, I wanted to pick up a tablet to try with the area I found.
Phew.
But I don't...
I don't want to use my, um...
I don't want to get rid of my ambrosia.
I guess I could get rid of...
No, I'm going to need invisiblium.
I think I'll need everything, every help I can get against this guy I'm about to face.
Uh oh.
Oh!
Oh, that was close!
That could have been real bad.
Imagine if I died there.
Oh, shit.
That would have been a death.
That would have been a death for the books.
Okay.
So now...
Uh, you know what?
I have an idea.
We're going to circumvent most of the bullshit in the ancient laboratory because I know exactly where this guy is, remember?
We encountered him.
Going straight there.
Is it night now?
The day-night cycle.
A little further up, I believe.
There it is.
My little wormhole.
Sneaky, sneaky.
So where was this guy?
Okoskivy.
I made a hole, didn't I?
We can find him down here.
Oh!
Here we are.
Sup, fool?
Ouch.
Oh, no!
I'm neutralized.
It's a disaster.
We gotta retreat.
That's such a sick debuff.
Do not.
Yeah.
Nice.
Oh, dude!
Dude, dude, dude, dude, dude.
I know what to do.
We're getting...
against this guy, man.
Let's make a pool of invisiblium.
And then we're gonna grab berserkium.
Nice.
No!
There we go.
Ow!
Oh, wait, they have that bullshit again.
So he's buffing him.
Shit.
Oh, easy, easy.
No problem.
This is what I need, man.
Berserkium is the...
is the little edge I need here in this fight.
My lack of damage is fixed with berserkium.
Telepor...
Ooh, teleportation!
Oh, I can't pick it up, though.
Wow, a broken wand?
Bro, these things take no damage.
From my damage type, at least.
Damn.
Probably not worthy to do all that.
Are you fireworking?
What's going on?
Is that you?
Oh, shit.
We got a buff, man.
Gotcha.
Nice.
Pheromone.
Ooh.
I don't know about...
Oh, here we go.
Fuck, I'm scared.
Drink...
a bunch of this.
88 seconds should be okay.
Let's fucking go.
Worst case, we retreat.
We dig.
We assume the worm form.
Where are you?
Is he up there?
No, that's someone else.
I want to kill him, though.
In case he buffs the boss.
Yeah, he missed me.
Oh, shit, there we are.
Whoa!
Yeah, that's scary.
That's scary.
Okay, okay.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Okay, wait for the shield to go down.
Here we go, here we go.
Do some damage, leave.
Shit!
I'm gonna have to fight!
Okay, run, don't panic, don't panic, don't panic.
Just run, just run.
Run for now, run for now, run for now.
Don't panic, don't panic.
It's okay, it's okay.
Back to the boss room.
We do a quick heal.
Did my shield absorb?
Wait, unless it's because I'm pheromone and...
I'm actually not happy about my spot here.
There's really no place to go here.
I need somewhere where I can hide.
Fuck me.
Can I make holes here?
I can.
Good, okay.
All I needed to know.
Okay, my dude.
Where are you?
You're somewhere over here.
Where?
Also, I need to drink more of this.
Bro, where are you?
Polymorphine.
Did this guy go all the way to the right or something?
Oh yeah, I think he did.
No, wait, that's a...
Oh, there he is.
I damaged him a little bit there.
Oh shit, I gotta be on the move, be on the move at all times.
Always be on the move.
Okay, his shield is down.
Hit him, leave.
Yep.
Whoa!
Leave.
Okay, okay.
Shit, shit, shit.
Worm tactics.
Where'd he go?
I need to heal.
Fuck yeah, look at the healing on that, bro.
Takes a bit of practice to do this.
There we go.
Okay.
Where'd you go?
Sir?
Where'd he go?
Did he fucking disappear again?
Bro, I had him!
No!
Fucking coward, come back here!
Oh wait, no, no.
There you... oh wait, he...
Motherfucker!
Wait, did he make a huge hole?
He made a huge hole here.
And he's healed again.
Get rid of the shield, come on.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
Okay, where are you?
Dammit.
Okay, I'm learning his attacks.
Worm tactics?
Yeah, come in here.
Come in here, buddy.
Oh wait, he's just digging through.
He doesn't give a fuck.
Shit.
Worm tactics?
It's working.
Sort of.
Okay, we hit him a little bit there.
Careful, careful.
Yep, yep, yep, yep, yep.
Shit.
Okay, okay.
Where are you now?
You're there?
Okay.
You want to follow me?
Did he just get hit by the vertical laser up there?
I think he did.
Okay, okay.
Worm tactics?
Come on, come on.
Come to me, come to me.
That's what I'm talking about.
A bit more, come on.
Shit, I hit myself.
Good damage.
Oh, be careful here now, be careful.
The fuck is that?
Worm tactics?
Just kite him around, kite him around.
Oh, we're slimed.
Come on.
Take it easy.
Wait for him.
Shield us down.
He's almost there.
Shit.
That's what I'm talking about!
Let's see what we got.
Crystal key!
Oh my God, what is this?
Mu, Seda, Omega?
Alpha.
Alpha, Omega.
Greek letters.
Get rid of something.
Oh, my heart is beating, dude.
That was insane.
Oh my God.
No, wait, I want this.
Get rid of this one.
Get rid of that one.
Get rid of...
that one.
What's this?
Cast copies of every spell in your wand.
Whoa!
Every spell.
Damn.
Oh, wait, how much mana does it cost, though?
320?
There's no way that's useful.
I mean, unless you have, like, a sick wand, I guess.
Oh, copies a random spell in another wand, you're holding.
10 mana drain.
Okay, at least 10 mana drain.
Every modifier-type spell in the current wand is applied to a projectile.
What?
Hold on.
Every modifier-type spell in the current wand is applied to a projectile.
Type others, so it's the...
Hmm.
That seems insane, but it adds .83 cast delay.
Holy shit.
Oh, what's the last one?
Cast a copy of the first spell in your wand.
Huh.
Okay.
So what is the difference between that and...
Oh, I guess...
It's more reliant, I guess.
This is a random, right?
Cast a random spell among the spells in your wand.
But this one...
You can sort of, I guess...
You can sort of, um...
Plan for this, right?
In a way.
All right.
Well, that was cool.
He dropped the key.
Drink that.
Throw that away.
Boink.
A crystal key.
The key is voiceless.
Hmm.
Do I know of a place that needs a key?
Let's think about this.
Do we have a place with a door of some sort or a keyhole?
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
I don't know.
I can't think of it right now.
Maybe we do.
Maybe not.
Uh, I'm gonna take each of these.
These seem important.
Let me get rid of...
I'm keeping the Holy Lands because I have a feeling I can make a crazy wand out of it somehow at some point.
Maybe the black hole I get rid of?
Or I can get rid of...
That one?
Yeah, fuck it.
Give me these.
I'm gonna put them somewhere safe.
You know what?
I'm gonna make a home base.
I think the first holy mountain is gonna be my home base.
Fuck yeah, guys.
I owned his ass.
That was amazing.
For a second I thought he disappeared on me again.
Now I wonder if he ever did disappear the other time or if he just went somewhere and I didn't find him again.
I guess that's possible.
You know?
But, uh...
Not this time, motherfucker.
I got you.
So for sure the strategy against that guy?
Is to get some sort of wand that has a huge damage on one click.
You know?
Because as soon as you hit him, he puts his shield back up.
So if you only do like 50 damage per shot or something but you shoot really fast?
It's actually not great.
For that guy you need something big.
Slow and heavy.
Like your mom.
I'm sorry.
Wait, whoa, whoa, whoa.
There's another drawing there.
Look at that.
What have I uncovered?
Is that called misilma?
Wait a minute.
Can you stop making noise?
Oh, he's buffed now as well.
Never mind.
He's gone.
Man, he was getting buffed from below as well.
That seems fair.
Look at this right here.
Isn't that interesting?
Nah, I don't want to kill these things.
Takes forever.
Okay, so now the question is what's the next step?
You know what I want to do?
Speaking of making tunnels, right?
I want to do the following.
Hold on.
I basically want to... So I've been making tunnels going like this way, that way, all kinds of ways.
But I want to try... Whoops.
But I want to try and make a tunnel.
Remember when I tried over here?
But then I ended up killing myself.
I had one HP.
I want to try that again over there.
I just want to dig in some direction forever and see what I find.
That's the next big thing.
But, first, I want to go see if I can't make a nice wand with my holy lance.
My advanced holy lance.
Wait, why did I take damage?
Something's going on in there.
What the fuck is that aura?
That's just a damaging aura, it seems.
Is that you doing that?
What's that?
Oh, you bastard.
Wait, hold on a second.
There's lava and tempered glass.
Is this a puzzle?
Hold on.
Oh wait, there's another...
Okay, so this is not uncommon.
Or this is common, I mean.
I thought maybe I found something big, but it's actually just decoration, I guess.
Fuck you.
What's happening in there?
Uh-oh.
Okay.
Oh, dude, I also want to...
Oh, but I need teleport.
I want to go into the heavens.
Above the pond.
Like the drawing.
But I can't get up there without teleport.
Wait.
These fuckers are buffing each other.
That's hardly fair.
Come here.
Are they even damaging me at all?
Are they aggressive?
They're just standing there.
Now that he's on my side, are you still...
Okay, seems like they can punch.
It's good to know.
Nah, I'm not going to go in there.
Whoa.
Oh man, I also want to go to the wizard's den again.
Maybe I should do that first.
Before I do the whole digging.
Operation.
In any case, I want to go see if I can't make a sick wand.
A circular.
Will you stop making bones?
So the crystal key, man.
Dude, I know what to use it for!
I know what to use it for!
Remember we found a chest we couldn't open?
It was in the sky!
It's got to be that!
What else could it be?
I mean, of course it could be other things.
But it's got to be that one!
It was totally a chest we couldn't open.
Also, just bathe in this.
I don't know why I'm avoiding it as if it's toxic or something.
But still, I need, um...
For that to happen, I need teleport.
I need to damn teleport!
Oh shit, it's actually so dark in there, I can't see anything.
Nevermind.
When you have such a good digging wand, you don't give a shit about anything.
Just go.
I'm shaving off the mountainside here.
Giving it a shave.
It's beautiful.
Okay.
Let's get to the holy temple.
Oh, this one is also destroyed.
Is there still a worm on the loose somewhere?
I get the feeling there is.
Actually, you know what I think I should do?
I should go to the wizards then first.
Because that place has insane amounts of wands.
That whole area, you know?
And there's a chance I may find teleport there.
So that could be the next big step.
Okay.
I'm gonna try and make something with the holy lands.
Or the... yeah, the holy lands.
Let's see.
What is the best wand I have for this?
So this costs 120 mana.
This one has a lot of mana, but very slow mana charge.
But if this is the sort of... if I make a...
Let's say I make a wand that is intended to do, like, pretty much one shot people.
Right?
Then I don't need to be spamming it quick.
It needs to be a puff, like a sniper shot, essentially.
So...
I need to do something like that.
I could put this on it, but that is risky, man.
Because you can kill yourself.
No, and I need that for the healing spell.
So that's not happening.
Holy lands.
I do have damage plus and speed up.
Let's just do something simple here.
Put this here.
Holy lands.
And speed up.
Maybe not on this wand.
Let me switch it back, even though it's sub-optimal for the digging.
Oh, it's so much better, look.
Compared to no speed.
Oh, yikes.
Oh, yeah.
And it does sick damage.
Let's see the damage.
Oh, wait, there's no statue there.
Okay, so how can we make it better?
Add a critical on it, maybe.
But here's the thing.
Is it ever going to be better than what I have here?
This is already really good.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Yo.
Wait a sec.
Does that disappear when it hits something?
Oh, it does.
No, wait, wait, wait.
If it goes through someone.
Let's check with the statue.
I'm scared of it hitting me now.
Okay, so it...
Okay, shit.
So what we need...
Is to add piercing to that, right?
So it goes plop, plop, plop, plop, plop, plop.
Through all the enemies.
That would be dope.
I also feel like I should utilize the spark bolt with double trigger.
I think I'm going to stick to my wand here.
I feel like I need more stuff to make this viable, such as add mana.
It's pretty much required.
I want to replace this with a bigger one like that.
I also feel like I should make this a little more reliable, because right now it is good.
But it's not like, amazing.
It takes a bit of practice to actually get hit by that.
If I can make the projectile slower somehow.
What do I have for that?
Maybe I have something here.
Sparkly bounce.
Double scatter?
No.
Wait, energy shield?
What the fuck is that?
Oh, wait a minute.
This actually amplifies the speed when I shoot.
Remember?
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Protectile speed point four, baby!
Is it enough?
Oh, wait, it's sort of weird.
Wait, what?
Oh, it's much more...
That's how we do it.
That's the way you shoot it up from now on.
And it's like, guaranteed.
That's the way.
Fuck yeah.
All right.
Now that's taken care of.
Yeah, so this wand is good.
All I need, though, and I say this, like, you know, all I need is some add mana.
Because then I can add this and it will go insane-o style.
So I'm good.
This is the perfect setup.
The perfect setup.
I don't want to put an extra here because it's going to shoot this one and then the next one is going to shoot without any of these.
So, you know, not amazing.
But what about these again?
Cast copies of every spell and you want.
Wait, of every spell?
Oh, wait a minute.
I have an idea.
Instead of doing this, we could do this.
Wait, does that include itself?
Because I'm thinking we need all of these three modifiers to affect this.
But if we use this, we get all the modifiers again on the next one.
I guess we can test with something simple.
What is something simple?
Maybe I'm being a bit stingy here.
Oh, wait, we need two of them.
Oh, we have two of them.
Perfect.
Do this and do that.
Okay, so without this, watch this.
The first one is going to be blood-lusted, ping pong path and projectile energy shielded.
Right?
Watch.
Yep, but the next one is just going to be a spark bolt.
But now...
there.
Oh, no, it doesn't show me exactly what happens.
Wait, so it... oh, dude.
It does cast... okay, so... okay, this is what's happening, okay?
It's casting bloodlust, ping pong, PES, I'm going to call it, on one spark bolt first.
And then when I shoot it again, it's actually doing this and this one itself again.
So it's actually casting itself.
So it doesn't lie when it says every... or a copy of every spell in your wand.
Dude.
Oh, I don't have enough mana.
But I would essentially duplicate this entire thing again.
Oh, but it also adds a lot of cast delay.
We can't forget that.
So actually it's not useful there.
Unless we can somehow remove that cast delay.
Okay, so we found a way to do it.
Oh, but wait, we don't even need... we don't even need to put this one here.
We just do that?
Right?
Wait.
It shoots these first, and then it shoots that, which is all of this again.
Let's test.
That's one.
Two.
Hey, fuck yeah!
That's amazing.
Oh, but wait, the whole idea was that I wanted to put two of these in here.
Wait, I'm not actually gaining anything by doing this.
I need to have this here.
Otherwise, I'm not like gaining the benefit of having twice the spells in here.
Unless I add...
one more.
Hold on, what does this do?
Copies a random spell in another one, you're holding.
That is just... stupid, isn't it?
That's really funny.
Hold on, if I do this...
This is gonna... do that.
But then it's gonna shoot two spells now.
Wait.
Oh yeah, yeah.
But is that actually something I want?
I don't think it is.
Unless...
This cast... this cost two mana.
Why would I do this?
No, it doesn't make any sense what I'm doing.
Because, no.
The whole idea was that I could have more than one of these in here, so I didn't have to come back to base all the time, right?
But this is just gonna make it bad, because I'm gonna take...
one twenty-something damage every time then, because I'm gonna get hit by two of them.
And I don't follow the exact same path.
So it doesn't actually make any sense.
This is the way to go.
Okay.
What were the other ones?
Every modifier-type spell in the current one is applied to a projectile.
Oh, but this one...
This is the one I need.
Look.
Oh, wait.
There.
Oh, this is actually exactly what I needed.
Watch.
One.
Yeah.
That's it.
That's exactly what I needed.
Fucking perfect.
So now, I'm just gonna waste these now just to test, but...
It's gonna shoot one.
Right?
Used one of them.
Then it's gonna shoot the next.
Wait, why is it...
Why is it using from that one?
It should be using from this one.
Wait, hold on.
One.
No!
Unless when this hits zero, it's gonna go over to that one.
You know what?
Let's just try this.
Because maybe that's the case.
When this hits zero, maybe it's gonna utilize this.
Yeah.
Fuck it.
Okay.
Now...
It's time to go to the Wizards then.
Let me also remove this stuff here.
To be determined, right now, by the way.
Like that.
So right now, I am...
I guess I'm here.
Oh, you can't see my cursor.
I guess I'm here right now.
This is the very first one.
Oh wait, is there an easy way down?
Uh...
No, you know what?
I wanna go over here.
I didn't finish exploring there and there were a ton of wands.
That is my chance to get teleport.
Yeah.
So I'm gonna take a trip on the surface until I reach the tower, approximately.
And then I'm gonna go down.
Oh yeah, that's perfect.
Switch it back.
Good.
Confirmed.
Back up we go.
Awesome.
Oh wait, where did I go up?
Oh, I never made the hole here, didn't I?
Shit.
Or did I?
Ah, ah, ah.
Thank you, worm.
Thank you very much.
Beautiful stuff there.
Let's not hurt ourselves.
Let's go.
Imagine if we died to that Ubusquibi right now.
Wouldn't that be funny?
I'm still prepared to lose everything in an instant, by the way, because this is Noita.
Fuck!
I was using casts of these right now.
Wait, how did that get to 10?
It was at 11 before.
So it does use it.
What?
I'm so confused by that.
Some of these combinations in this game make so little sense to me.
It is also possible that I'm just not remembering that it was 10 before.
But I'm pretty sure it was 11.
So I think it does use both somehow.
But maybe if I only shoot fast after each other, if I wait like I did before, maybe that's different.
Okay, so instead of going around the top, I'm gonna go a shortcut here.
Because I can.
Look at that.
Ah, yeah.
I don't know why, but maybe drinking beer, getting a little tipsy has been helping me out, actually, today.
Because I feel like I've been playing well.
Like, I owned that fucking yalke misti.
And you can't tell me I didn't, because that shit was flawless.
We also got a...
Okay.
Maybe we should do that now.
We can try the music stuff.
I marked them all, didn't I?
Hold on.
One there, on the right.
Here.
Two.
Oh, shit.
Three.
Ah, four.
Yep, I got them all.
We could do that.
But maybe it's one of those things where, so they play a song, and after a while they stop.
So maybe you need to be super fast and have them all active at the same time or something.
So if that, just in case that is the case, I will wait until I find a teleport one, and then I'm gonna go nuts.
We're gonna try that at that point.
That's my current idea for that.
Okay.
Awesome.
To the tower we go.
Look at our HP, man.
This is the best run I've had.
No doubt about it.
This tree has a hole in it.
Ah, so painfully slow.
When you're just walking.
Imagine if you can find a dune bike in this game and just vroom, vroom around.
Honestly wouldn't surprise me.
It really wouldn't.
I destroyed cacti.
I have been sent to eradicate all cacti of these lands.
Oh, wait, whoa, whoa, whoa.
We also gotta try the demon eye on top of the pyramid.
I'm gonna do that on my way over there.
That was the same symbol.
I bet you it's gonna be platforms, just like the ones we saw in the west.
Come on.
Yeah, look at that.
Are you ready?
Watch.
Yes.
Oh, I can barely not make it.
Hold on, I have an idea.
Yeah, the skills.
Oh, easy.
No!
Shit!
This is most likely just gonna lead me back up to that place I already know exists, and I'm gonna get my ass kicked.
Well, we're gonna try anyway.
Wait, why is no more sound?
No more sound.
Oh, there we go.
It's back.
Oh, yeah, here we are.
Cloudscape.
Whoa, shit!
Are we okay up here?
Are we gonna get up?
Whoa, I can't even destroy the cloud.
Huh?
Oh, they punch holes in the clouds, though, can I?
My digging does nothing.
These clouds are made of the hardest material ever.
This guy has a handgun, it seems.
He's wearing a mask.
Holy shit.
Wait, do I took damage when I hit them?
It's so weird.
Oh, no, it's not one of those.
It's one of those fuckers.
I hate that.
Wait, I'm stuck.
Ah, I can't move.
Man, I don't do a lot of damage to these guys.
What the fuck is that?
Oh, no.
Wait, they're not gonna damage me, right?
I'm okay?
Yeah, they're my pals.
We're okay.
Oh, no, you're not my pal.
Definitely not my pal.
What, what, what, what, what, what, what?
What's happening?
I'm ready to GTFO here, by the way, guys.
I'm ready to just leave.
They are shooting something at me.
Oh, no, no, no.
Whoa!
That is a mess.
Wait, maybe this does sick damage to them.
No.
Holy shit.
Whoa, what, what, what?
I got teleported.
I got teleported?
Oh, dude, this is, we gotta get to the chest.
I should be close here.
It was somewhere on the right.
I remember that much.
Uh-oh.
Got you.
Fucking teleporting bitch.
Ah, not again.
I'm getting better at that.
Wait, go to here?
Oh, this is it.
Tell me it works.
The four essences represent the four elements that form this visible world.
In build with their terrible power, one may do great deeds.
But one should be afraid of their destructive might.
To this end, we have devised a way to remove these dangerous forces.
Seek it in the west and east.
A legend also tells that all the elements originated from the Egg of Sky.
And return to it one day.
The Egg of Sky!
That's gotta be the intro cinematic!
Also, the essences has gotta be the things that I pick up and I go explosion.
Boom, boom, boom.
And then, one should be afraid of their destructive might.
To this end, we have devised a way to remove them essence eaters.
That's it.
Does it work?
Hey, are you gonna be...
Huh?
If he hits me, am I dead?
Heh, heh.
Okay, he seems passive enough.
Maybe he needs to...
Shit.
Hey, you like keys?
Heh!
Hey, you there?
Huh?
Didn't even damage him.
No!
No, my key!
Fuck!
No!
Okay, it clearly didn't work.
But I think I know what's going on here.
I think I know how to open this chest.
It says the four essences.
Right?
So, we know there's an essence somewhere on the right.
Because we found it.
We know there's an essence in the west.
There must be two more somewhere.
So, what I think is going on here is that I need to grab all of them.
Maybe I need to have all four essences on me.
To like, prove my worth or something.
You know, that if you can survive that shit, and you can get here, congrats.
You get the chest.
And maybe the key is for something completely else.
But I don't know, I mean, it says coral chest.
Also, I need to take a picture of this with my phone.
Hold on.
There we go.
I have a picture now.
Alright.
Also, is the sun going down?
Is the sun set right now?
What's happening?
No!
We're fine.
It was somewhere up here, I believe.
Ah, this is going to be super difficult.
Oh wait, no, no, I can dig, I can dig.
Also, you know what?
I'm going to go grab my key before I actually forget about it.
And get rid of that.
Boink!
I have you documented now.
Oh, tell me the key didn't fall all the way down.
Oh, the key couldn't be anywhere.
Let's do some detective work here.
I threw it from up here.
Oh no.
Ow, ow, ow.
Stop that.
Okay, so I threw it from here.
It fell like this, right?
It should be somewhere...
It should be close to here.
It must have fallen all the way down.
What's that?
Oh wait, what?
I think that key is gone.
At least, I don't know where it is right now.
It could even be buried in the sand.
I really fucked up.
I really fucked that one up, guys.
Shit.
But that's okay.
That's okay.
I'll find it at some point.
The next thing I want to do is...
What was it, what was it?
Right.
I want it to go down.
Into the overgrown place.
But let me quickly check the top of the pyramid.
Just in case the key fell up there.
What are the chances it landed right on top of the pyramid?
I think it's somewhere up in the clouds, if I'm honest.
Yeah, rip.
Oh well.
I feel like I'm way more comfortable against Yalchimisti now, so...
If I ever get to meet him again in the future, in another run...
I guess I will have a better time.
I know how to dodge him now.
I just need to play Ring Around the Rosie with him.
Oh, hold on.
I needed to go to the tower.
That was the whole plan.
To the tower.
Can I... No, I can't dig this.
Oh man, my fingers are starting to hurt a little bit.
I wish I could slide down here on a skateboard.
Or a sled.
Teleportation.
If I want to try and pick it up with a flask, but I don't have one.
I mean, I have water, but I kind of need that water.
Or do I?
Now that I'm fire immune.
I mean, I guess it's nice to convert toxic shit.
But for now, I think I can survive without the water.
Let me try and pick it up.
Let's see if this is possible.
Because I have something I want to try with the teleportation anyway.
Shit.
Did I fill it?
1% rock?
Say what?
I ate the rock.
Fantastic.
Shit.
No, no, no, no, no.
Fill it.
Oh wait, it's not even deep enough to fill, I guess.
Yeah, this is a fool's errand.
I need a deeper pool if I am to fill this flask.
Look at that, the essence eater.
There's also one in the west, in the snowy region.
So we have the scale.
I should add that, by the way.
Not just the scale, but also...
In fact, I'm going to copy what I have on the left.
Not the prettiest drawing in the world, but it'll do.
No.
Wait, wait, wait, this is not right.
I'm an idiot.
It's the essence eater that's here.
Shit.
And that was simply a...
Hold on.
It was a structure.
And then we had this sort of
essence eater.
Boink.
Beautiful.
And then we have a scale.
Which looks like that.
Okay.
That's like a stick.
The ball at the end.
And then it goes sort of...
Eh, I'm not happy about that one.
Not happy about that one either.
Better.
And there's just sand on it.
And then there's this weird platform here.
Good enough.
Maybe make it a bit smaller.
There.
To be prettified later.
Nice.
And there's got to be something about this as well.
You know?
Like...
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't know.
Let's get to tower.
And now I want to go down and find myself a teleport.
That is my goal right now.
Finding a teleport.
I'm going to murder people.
Left and right.
It's going to be fun.
We're back in this place.
I don't think I ever went to the right.
At least not very much.
Kind of a sick wand.
I don't like this sound that's coming out.
Is that a kivaskibi?
What's that?
Oh, shit.
Oh, wait, I'm immune.
Well, I'm almost immune.
I'm not immune to the frost.
Whoa, but the explosions themselves.
Oh, this place is much more safe for me now that I have this perk.
This is lovely.
Oh.
Holy shit, it's just raining toads.
Mushroom, I mean.
Are they...
coming from?
I don't understand.
Whoa.
Good thing I'm explosion immune.
Holy shit, I kind of want to try and get high.
Maybe it works here.
But I got to get rid of these guys first.
Oh, we got a wand.
And some health.
Lovely.
And a kivaskibi, that's not so lovely.
Whoa, mana charge speed of a thousand.
If only it had more slots so I can put all this stuff on it.
One, two, three, six slots.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Damn it.
But it is a good wand.
This is a great wand.
Maybe that would be really nice.
I don't even know.
Let's get rid of that one.
That's going to eat its way through the... all that.
What's happening over here?
Oh, that's the edge.
Okay, perfect.
That is the edge.
Kind of want to just keep digging this way.
Is that crazy?
If it is, then I want to be crazy.
Uh, nope.
Oh, my game is lagging a little bit now.
Stop growing.
Oh, maybe I stopped the growing.
Maybe we need to destroy the soil or something.
Maybe that's fertile land or something.
No, it just keeps happening.
I don't understand.
What's happening?
Blue fungus.
There it comes.
It just regrows.
Weird.
Oh, my God.
Two wands?
Black holes.
I think I found this wand before.
Chaotic path.
Let me see this.
It summons a spore pod that attaches to a surface and then grows and explodes into spikes.
So that is exactly what I'm witnessing happening here.
I just don't understand why it keeps happening.
That's the only...
confusion for me.
Dude, this place is just jam-packed with wands.
It's literally everywhere.
It's insanity.
Chaotic transmutation.
There's got to be a teleporter somewhere.
Right?
Not that one.
This is some trippy music.
Sounds like we're in some kind of spaceship.
A chainsaw!
Color me intrigued, actually.
I haven't had one of those.
Damage slice 13.
That is kind of... I think I need it.
I need it.
So the question is, can I make my way...
This is the problem when I don't have tinker with wands everywhere.
I will never find my way back here.
It's going to be a pain in the ass if I want to get this.
Hmm...
I mean, I can dig with this.
I can replace this for now.
Go back.
I think it's worth it.
So let me keep it straight here.
I'm going to go left no matter what.
No, wait, wait.
No, hold on.
This is actually easy.
It's easy to find this again.
Because I was close to the right wall.
Yeah.
Let me see the right wall.
It's somewhere over here.
There it is.
So it's right over the... So this should be easy to find.
And it's right next to this big pool of water.
Easy to remember.
Let's see what we got here.
A disc projectile.
And flammoxium.
I'm going to go back.
And deposit my...
Actually, no, I'm going to put my chainsaw in here.
I'm going to put a double and put digging bolt and chainsaw.
Because look, this costs one mana.
It's free damage, baby.
And there's HP here.
Thanks.
What's this?
Okay.
So I'm just going to go back.
And I already made a bunch of tunnels.
So this should be quite easy.
Let's berserk you.
Huh.
Rainbow glimmer.
Thunder charge.
Had a lot of mana on it.
Hey!
No fucking way.
There's healing there.
Awesome.
And I have room for it.
Fuck yeah.
I'll take one more, I think.
Get rid of that.
Give me that, thank you.
Anything here?
Nope.
So I've been here already.
Holy shit.
Explosion on drunk enemies.
Yeah, I don't know about that.
So it looks like these enemies here, like this whole region is just insanity because everyone just respawns.
It feels like no matter how many I kill, they come back.
And cause disturbances.
Like it's never ending.
What's that?
Yellow slime?
I've never seen that.
This area is insane.
Okay, here we are.
Let's find the tunnel.
It should be up here somewhere.
There's no way I'm re-digging that tunnel.
I can tell you that much.
Oh yeah, right.
I was intrigued by that one because it would reduce recoil, but I'm actually utilizing the recoil because I have no teleport.
So the recoil is quite welcome.
Man, I...
This place is huge.
Here it is.
There's still fire here, by the way.
How is that still burning?
Come on.
Oh, I'm stuck.
Oh, and now I'm in the sand cave.
Oh, tell me I made a tunnel on the left side here, too.
I think I did.
Oh, but wait, that was right into the boss area.
Wasn't it?
Shit.
Maybe I just leave normally, then.
I mean, it's not gonna be hard to leave normally.
Yeah.
Also, let's field test this now.
Watch.
So easy to apply.
The healing, guys.
This is the best healing I've ever had.
Not only does it heal my wounds, but it also heals my soul.
Oh, I'm slimed up.
You know what I really need?
I need teleport with a long distance cast.
Oh, baby.
That would be amazing right about now.
I feel like I should maybe have explored the overgrown area a bit more before I left.
Just in case I did find a teleport.
There were just wands everywhere.
So maybe I can just imagine I go back now to apply the chainsaw.
Then I come back to overgrown, and the first wand I find is gonna be a teleport wand.
I can imagine it.
Man, my hands are sweaty for some reason.
I think it's because I've never been this far in the game, you know?
But I'm ready to die.
I'm ready to lose it all.
This run has already been amazing.
Even if I were to die right now, I would be satisfied.
I discovered so much.
Literal insanity.
The question is, can I dig down here somewhere and make it quicker?
Because I did come from below at some point.
But if I get where I came from, it was not here.
Was it?
No, it was not here.
Here.
That's it.
Oh!
Wait, no, no, no.
I'm scared of the boss.
We're not going anywhere near that place.
I don't know exactly what triggers that guy, but...
I'm not going anywhere near.
I'm too afraid.
Do I have a double with me?
Shit!
Oh, but I have a quadruple.
I guess I can use that in a pinch.
Oh, but that costs five mana.
Fuck!
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Hopefully there's a double spell in the holy mountain.
That's the only requirement I need right now.
Or a bifurcation.
I don't have that either.
Come on.
Off we go.
God, I'm painfully slow.
And the sun is just... bearing down on me hard.
And I'm wearing this robe as well.
It's just...
You get sweaty in this robe, you know?
You get swamp ass.
You get peat ass.
Okay, here we are.
Okay.
What a detour, huh?
Kind of want to make a... Oh, you know what?
You know what?
I have an idea.
Oh, I only have this here.
Oh, but I have a great idea, guys.
I'm going to make a shortcut back to...
So check this out.
This is my plan.
Because we lack teleport wand, I intend to make the shortest of shortcuts you've ever shorted, okay?
So we are going to be ending up... here?
Oh, but wait.
I was about to say, let's just dig straight through.
But maybe that's not feasible because there's a fucking literal lake of lava in the way.
And I was thinking, we could use the black hole to do it if we put speed up on it.
And we're going to use one of those spells to duplicate it so we can have more than one.
You know, so we get more for the cost of one.
But now that I look at this, it's actually not that great.
Unless I snowy depth from the right.
Shortcut all the way.
Yeah, I don't know.
But watch this.
Do we have a double spell here?
Double, double, double spell somewhere?
Double scatter spell.
There it is.
Beautiful.
Throw that shit away.
Gimme.
So this is the plan.
Instead of having this here, we're going to go boop and swoop.
And the reason is, this costs one mana.
This costs zero mana.
That's actually great.
But we're getting 13 damage.
Hold on, let me see if I understand this.
Trigger.
When it collides, it shoots modifiers up the wazoo on the double scatter spell.
So both of these get these modifiers.
Oh yeah, this is going to be sick.
Hold on.
Oh yeah!
And look at this!
Without the... Watch.
No chainsaw.
So that in itself is adding an incredible amount of damage.
Wild.
Holy shit.
That's amazing.
Okay.
I have one black hole.
Did I store more black holes here?
Maybe.
Uh, what's this?
Drilling shot?
Gives a projectile the power to go through the ground.
Hold on.
Remind me again exactly what that means?
The fuck, what do you mean?
Let me go over here.
Oh, wait, I think I know what it means.
Right.
Right, I know what it means.
Okay.
It doesn't actually drill.
It just sort of, you know, faces through it a little bit.
It's a bit weird.
Power to go through the ground.
I wonder if that is at any... Oh, I don't have my digging wand on me.
But it's in the overgrown area.
I guess it could be cool to experiment with.
To see if that will make the digging more insane.
Because you dig more area in front of you.
Even though you're already walking at max speed when you dig.
So it wouldn't really increase the speed at which you do things.
Technically.
Uh...
Nice.
What else?
Let's try the black hole stuff.
So I have cast a copy.
Oh, wait a minute.
Now I needed my cast three copies.
Fuck.
Oh wait, I have it.
This is one copy?
Where are my three copies?
Where are my three copies at?
Why did I... I must have it somewhere.
Fuck.
Why would I bring this and... Hold on, where did I leave my three copies?
I must have left it at the alchemisty.
Shh.
Why did I leave that one and not this one?
Of all things.
That was stupid.
Anyway, I don't think it's gonna be enough anyway.
Like, with one speed up on it.
Black hole.
Can we make it?
Okay, watch this.
Protectile energy shield, baby.
Look, without this.
I'm gonna put on spark bolt now just to illustrate my point.
Um... Get rid of that.
So watch.
Without this?
It's like...
This, okay?
It's kind of fast.
But...
With this.
Wait, is it faster?
Let's try with the holy lands.
It's probably better to illustrate.
So, no, this is not on now.
Kind of slow.
But now.
Even slower.
Wait.
Hold on, it's not working.
I know it works with the black hole.
Hold on.
Do I have a spell refresh, just in case?
No.
Eh, I need to nail this.
The question is, should I put this on before or after?
That's like the big one.
Let me think.
So this one, if I remember correctly...
It accelerates it.
And then...
I guess it doesn't matter, because both are being applied at the same time.
Doesn't matter.
I'm trying to remember if this is the one that accelerated the black hole, or if it was the projectile repulsion field that I had on, which was a perk.
I seem to remember it was def...
Oh, wait, no, no, it was the frontal deflection perk I had, I believe.
Because I remember this always being on.
This is not working the way I think.
No, we need to speed on it.
But we can duplicate it once, I guess.
Copy's a random spell.
The first spell.
That's not technically a spell, is it?
Is it, though?
Oh, every spell.
That's the one I need.
Here we go.
So if I... not here, I need to do it somewhere...
Wait a minute.
So I am in the coal pits now.
You know what?
If I do it...
And we have to remember, I actually did go down a bit.
Right, so we... and my proportions are probably completely out of whack.
So, I'm just gonna dig right.
Fuck yeah.
And then we can take the rest with the...
We do the rest...
with the laser cutter.
Let's go.
I'm gonna do it all the way at the top.
Just so it's easy to remember.
Right here.
Oh my god, the digging is wild.
How far did it go?
Oh, it's not even that great, actually.
My map is accurate!
Holy shit!
It was accurate!
Fuck!
Good thing I didn't go any further with that.
I would have brought lava down on me.
Holy shit!
Oh, no.
I gotta go further down to do this shit.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck off.
Oh, man.
Fuck me.
Yeah.
So, actually...
My map is precisely...
Fuck me!
I changed it again.
I'm sorry, but it was quick this time.
I apologize.
I guess I can keep it on now.
I basically wanted to show you was this.
So, my map is actually accurate.
Look at this.
Because I dug from here.
And what did I hit?
Lava.
This is actually insane.
But if I dig from the bottom, it should be fine.
Right?
That's what I'm thinking.
Also...
Wait.
Right.
Formation bifurcated.
I feel like that should be...
This should be really helpful in some situation.
I just can't think of what that situation might be.
The return spell is something that intrigues me greatly.
Wait a minute.
Did I pass the...
Did I go too far here?
No, there's no way.
Back up.
I have one black hole left.
I mean...
Okay, so the only way to really utilize black holes...
is to find a wand with like...
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
We found a wand with a bunch of white holes on it, right?
And I forgot about that.
I forgot where it was.
Oh, wait, wait.
Accelerating shot.
Forgot about this.
Let's test how good this is.
Holy shit!
Guys!
Wait, how far did it dig?
Holy shit!
Wait, what?
There's a wand.
It was in the wall!
That's the one I couldn't get before.
Wait, what?
Why do I have one left?
What's happening?
I don't understand.
Is this bugged?
Okay, guys, I'm gonna ask you right now.
Is this actually... Did I discover a bug?
Don't spoil anything.
I mean, just yes or no.
Did I discover a bug?
I'm gonna open chat in like 10 seconds.
Because I don't want to abuse this bug if it's actually a bug.
It's not a bug?
Fuck yeah, I don't get it, but okay, cool.
Oh, dude.
I was really considering abusing that bug.
I don't understand how this works, though.
Okay, well, that's okay.
I mean, I don't need to understand.
Why does that work?
No.
Ah, it only works with black hole.
I just wasted.
No!
What?
There's no way!
How is that fucking legal?
That can't be right.
That cannot be right!
That's broken as fuck!
Wait, why does that one go to zero, but this one goes to one?
Hold on, let me try and understand this.
It is that one doing it.
Cause the projectile to accelerate as it flies.
Hold on, casts copies of every spell...
in your wand.
It feels like a bug.
There's no fucking way.
Rock is back on the menu, boys!
Where's my rock?
It's somewhere.
It's gotta work with a rock!
I have homing.
Somewhere.
Dude.
I need to, I need to calm down.
This is fucking wild.
All right, we're making a tunnel.
We're making a tunnel.
Maybe, hold on, I don't even need this then.
I mean, it's nice, but maybe sometimes I don't want to shoot it that far.
Dude, this is my new digging wand.
I don't even need my old wand.
This is fucking crazy.
Wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No.
No way.
Wait a minute.
Oh!
Oh, that's funny.
It follows the...
What if I do this?
It follows...
Oh, wait, I understand what's happening.
The black hole is attracting the spell itself.
I thought it was like a modifier of some sort that it...
Do I need to stand in it though?
This is...
insane.
I don't even need this.
Hello?
This is fucking nuts.
I almost can't believe this.
Wait, have I been able to do this with the other spells that I had?
The ones that made... Hold on.
We need to try something.
This is very important.
Cast a random spell among the spell's new wand.
It doesn't work with this one.
What's the difference?
Oh, casts copies.
It's not... Oh, it's not the same.
Oh, I see.
Oh, actually it makes sense.
I didn't even realize it said copies.
I thought it was the same as this, but like...
Just variations on it, you know?
Oh, the first one or...
Spell from your other wand or whatever.
I get it.
That is insane.
How am I not completely overpowered right now?
Like, this is... this is...
Something else.
Entirely.
Now I'm thinking...
This.
I can probably make a cool ass wand with this as well.
Somehow.
Although this adds a bunch of castile.
I have to remember that.
Hold on, does this work as well?
Wait.
Oh my God!
What is happening?
This is completely fucked.
Uh...
Wow.
I guess I'm going with that.
Now I can heal all the time.
And I can dig all the time.
And every time I dig, I heal.
And every time I heal, I dig!
Wait, maybe I don't want to dig every time I heal.
But...
No, wait.
Uh...
Wait.
Maybe I do...
I don't need this!
I don't need laser!
Fuck the laser!
Dude!
I don't even need this anymore!
Black Hole is my new best friend!
This is... unrivaled insanity.
Um...
What else can I do?
Like, I feel like I just freed up a bunch of wands here.
This is awesome!
Uh...
Wait.
This costs 10 mana.
Now this is fine.
This one is good.
I don't need to modify anything here, I don't think.
This one is... this is a good one.
This is a good one.
Uh...
I could add...
Speed to this one now.
And then have the speed up on that.
How does that look?
Whoo!
It's still pretty far.
That's wild.
That is insanity.
Um... but maybe I can just put it here then, I guess.
Have more slots.
Holy shit.
Question is, what is... does it matter in which order this is?
Start slow.
Didn't I make it go much faster before?
Oh, I see.
Oh yeah, there we go, there we go.
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah.
We're launching that fucking shit to space!
Wow.
But you know what?
I'm gonna do this.
Oh no, wait, wait, no.
Because we don't have Tinker...
Because we don't have Tinker with Wands everywhere, I will limit the stuff on one wand.
So we don't need this, because we have unlimited.
It doesn't matter.
That's insane right there.
We don't even need to have more...
We don't even need this.
No, no, no, this goes here.
Much better.
We just go like that, boy.
That's fine, we don't need to walk faster!
That's totally okay.
And then these can be replaced with Wands we find in the wild.
Awesome.
We don't need these anymore.
This changes everything.
Absolutely everything.
Now, do I want it on this one or another one, though?
Let's just think about this.
Okay, so man, it's like that.
It's actually a good wand.
What is that?
Oh, Castile.
Oh, this is better.
This is the best wand for that.
Yeah, perfect, perfect.
All right, let's fucking go.
Let's fucking go.
This is wild.
My whole body is sweating right now from excitement.
Like, I'm a sweaty gamer right now.
Look at this.
I don't care at all.
Although...
We are going to run out of mana with this.
In fact, I changed my mind.
I'm going to put it on another wand.
And maybe give it some speed, just because we're doing this right now.
We're going to put acceleration on it.
And then later we can take it off.
Yeah.
That sounds cool.
I'm just afraid of breaking things...
that I shouldn't break.
So, no, I'm not going to put speed on, but I will put it on another wand, just because I don't like having this low mana situation, if we're going to do a lot of digging.
It's better to just wait for the recharge.
Because it's going to be ready when this one is done swinging, right?
Yeah, that's better.
That's better.
Let's go.
This is fucking great.
Unbelievable.
I'm unstoppable.
This is... I can't die.
How am I ever going to die?
Even better.
Imagine putting the healing on...
on your damage wand.
You can be unstoppable.
I beat the game.
It's over.
It's done.
Look at that.
Nothing can stop me.
Oh, but you know what the speed is nice for, if you have speed on this?
Is if you want to dig down, you make a super big hole, right?
And then just fall down through it.
Oh, no way, I'm here.
I guess that makes sense, given where we were.
That is fantastic.
We keep going.
I just have a huge grin on my face right now.
I look like a dumbass.
Wait, what's that?
There was a weird effect going on there just now, and I'm not sure it was my black hole.
Or what it was.
I think it was that way for some reason.
Then it shoots off.
Okay, we're back here now.
Let me put this on my normal digging keybind.
Like, what was that?
Whoop!
Shit.
I don't know where we are.
Just keep going.
Okay, the dig is not very straight here, unfortunately.
But it's okay.
I approximately know where I am.
Oh, hello there.
Oh, that's cool.
Oh, man, I do so much more damage.
My wand with the chainsaw has been upgraded immensely.
Okay.
What now?
This is the sand caves.
Also, I'm double-checking my OBS right now, just in case I don't have a map on.
I have, like, this paranoia now.
I think it's a good thing I have that paranoia.
I can't die.
I don't care about anything.
I guess if I get polymorph'd, that could be the end.
So, yeah.
But, dude, I feel like I have unlocked the ultimate knowledge of Noita right now.
Like, even if I die in a minute here, fuck it.
I know if I can get this fucking spell, I'm unstoppable.
Assuming I have some healing, of course.
Or something like that.
In other words, this was valuable knowledge.
Holy fuck.
I'm doing so much more damage.
It may not look like it to you, but I can feel it, trust me.
I know how much I do to these guys normally.
Now they just insta-die.
I love the effect of the black hole on the spells.
I remember, in the beginning of this game,
thinking, oh, there's no way to heal here.
This is like, oh, if you take damage, that's it, you know?
I mean, other than going to the holy mountain.
Oh, how wrong I was.
Okay, we're back.
But now, I guess I don't need to grab that wand anymore.
That wand is useless to me right now.
I don't fucking need it anymore.
But, I would like a teleport.
The big one we need.
The teleport.
Let's find one.
And then it's time to solve some goddamn mysteries in this world.
Whoa.
And we should get high as well.
Or should we?
I feel like we should not risk anything right now.
No.
No, no, no, no.
I just really want to.
Hehe, heal me up!
Piercing shot!
I guess I don't need it anymore.
Also reduces damage by 15.
Wait.
No, I do need this.
This would make... No, I don't need it because I have improved healing now.
Fuck.
But I guess I'll take it anyway, because I didn't have another wand.
I was still in the state of mind where I had the healing bolt wand.
What's that?
Mystery fungus.
Wait, the blue sand is turning into mystery fungus.
Eat it.
Okay, fuck it, we're getting high.
I'm too mis... I'm too mystified.
We gotta get high on the mystery fungus.
How can you not do that, right?
Nothing happens.
Okay.
Why don't I get the screen effect at all either?
It's so weird.
Whenever I have the balls to actually get high, the game won't let me for some reason.
It's very interesting.
Damn.
I'll take it.
Holy shit.
There's all kinds of shit on this one.
Nope.
I reject.
Which feels insane to me, but you know.
The old black hole is actually kind of nuts for crowd-controlling enemies.
Like, look at this.
Oh wait, it's not getting sucked up in it?
I thought it was.
Look.
It's cool though.
This is too much fun.
Reduce re... Oh, this is big.
Take it.
Homing.
Ooh.
We could make a rock wand.
Now that we have infinite rocks.
Is that good though?
I feel like, hmm.
Maybe it is.
I'll take it.
I think it's nice to have as an alternative, maybe.
You know, you have your normal damage wand, and then you have the rock wand.
If the situation calls for it, you bring out Dwayne Johnson.
And shit pops off, you know?
Green glimmer, no thanks.
Look at all the... This is truly the place to get wands.
Like, I thought maybe I got lucky before finding all those, but this is consistently a lot of wands.
What's that?
Plasma beam thrower.
That's a bit too wild for me, I think.
Get off of me.
Hahaha.
It's... Honestly, being able to fire black holes at any moment is the funniest shit ever.
It's such a power trip.
Such a nice fantasy I've had forever, you know?
What's that?
Knockback.
Cool.
I think I may have found that before.
Damn.
Okay.
Firebolts.
Hahaha.
Damn.
There it is.
Bunch of black holes.
Not that I need them now anymore.
Good wand though.
Oh, I've checked these already.
Let's go further down.
Okay.
Let's see how far down we can go here.
It's gonna be the new chest.
Whoa, what a chain reaction.
Wait, now I'm getting high?
Huh?
Whoa, it's like...
That's a delayed reaction, man.
That's like taking edibles, you know?
You're like, oh, I don't feel anything.
And then like half an hour later, you're like...
That's pretty much what this is.
Oh, I'm high as fuck now.
It's kicking in, boys.
We're tripping.
Holy shit.
Even looks like my projectiles are bending.
Oh, but I guess they are because of the black hole.
Oh, that's funny as hell.
Imagine the start of Noita when you spawn in and then compare this to this right here.
It's not even the same game.
The rules have changed now.
This is not Noita, this is Noi 2.
I'm at a solid Noi...
Noi 9 out of Noi 10.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What is all that?
In vesibilium, acid, all kinds of bullshit.
Whoa.
Holy shit, I'm high as fuck.
Dude, the black hole even absorbs the liquids.
It's incredible.
The black hole is not just for digging, it's for...
I don't even know.
Just getting rid of shit.
It's fantastic.
This guy's bleeding a lot.
Wait!
Polymorphine!
We're leaving!
Oh no, oh no.
I just got sober real quick.
Nope.
Oh, but wait, no, it's hitting me again now.
Oh yeah.
What are all these little things jumping on me?
Oh, I don't care, I can't die.
Holy shit, what's up, dude?
How you doing?
There's too many of these small frogs.
We got a wand.
Is that water?
It is.
Oh man, my wand has been severely upgraded with that chainsaw.
And what a simple combination it is as well.
That seems dangerous.
But not for me, because I'm immune.
Ooh, we jumped right into my face.
What was that?
Pheromone, I think.
Let's get high again.
We're not high enough.
I want to stay high.
You can't be in this place without being high.
That's the new rule.
This is the real experience.
Okay, I've checked on one already.
What is that up there?
Something.
I have a muscle spasm in my left...
hand.
Somehow.
It's weird.
Like, I can feel it vibrating, the muscle.
Feels odd.
Black holes for everyone.
Oh, I'm scared.
What's that?
Leggy mutation.
No, I don't...
That's a perk.
Also, what is that down there?
That's polymorphine.
No, thanks.
Nope, I don't want none of that.
In fact, let's not get high anymore, because I have trouble distinguishing liquids.
But here's the thing.
Black hole will absorb that, right?
This is the safe way to dispose of it.
Just throw into a black hole.
Sort of.
Oh my god.
Way too many enemies.
Let's just find some ones!
What's this?
Giant spitter bolt, reduce lifetime.
Oh.
Reduces castile as well.
That's kind of nice.
With a lot, actually.
Ooh.
Very neat.
But...
I don't want to replace my current.
Actually, I do.
Do I?
No.
I'll keep what I have.
We got another wand up there.
Let's keep healing.
Damn.
Homing plasma beam crosses.
Look at this one.
Very luminous.
Shiny like chrome.
I don't even need gold anymore.
I can't get any more perks.
And I can't buy anything anymore.
Unless I find a shop, I guess.
Which I guess is possible.
There could be shops.
Who knows?
Alright.
Oh, I have a twitchy...
No wait, why would I...
Was I drunk just now?
Maybe I had whiskey in my system.
Recall damper...
No.
None of that for me, please.
I'm not even carrying water anymore.
That's how crazy this whole thing has become.
That's ambrosia.
I checked that one already, I think.
Yep.
Let's keep going down.
Oh yeah, look at all these wands.
They're everywhere.
Hey!
Don't mind if I do!
An extra one of those can have like insane effects.
Because it stacks like multiplicatively, I guess, when you add them together like that.
Well, it's just adding, I guess, in that case.
But the fact that it's shooting so fast makes it do so much more damage, right?
Or double the amount, I guess.
Basically double the damage.
Never mind what I said.
What's that?
Anti-homing?
That seems bad.
Ow!
Kind of want to just go right, I can easily dig now.
But wait, no, no, no, we need teleport.
We need teleport to solve the mysteries of this game.
Water to poison?
Yeah, how about no?
How about poison to water?
How about them apples?
That's something I would immensely enjoy.
We did it!
Fuck yeah!
There we go!
And it's already primed!
We're fucking rocking and rolling right now!
Holy shit!
Let me just quickly check these ones as well, and then we're out of here.
This is awesome!
Awesome.
What's that?
Oplasma beam orbit!
Damn.
This place is huge!
This is way bigger than I thought it would be.
Alright, we go right now.
Shit!
I shouldn't have broke that.
But I guess there was just freezing liquid in there.
What the fuck is all this?
Jesus Christ!
Look at this wand!
Orbiting arc...
I don't need any of this!
No!
In a past life maybe, but here?
Now?
No.
Okay, so here's the plan.
I do want to dig to the right, but I'm going to do it in a...
in a predictable place where I can always get back to it.
I'm going to do it at the top.
Well, sort of.
Almost at the top.
Holy shit, another one.
Wow.
I did let go of homing, so the rock dream is dead for now, but we can always get it back.
Wait, what?
Wait a second.
Oh...
Hello!
What do we got here?
Moon radar?
It's a perk!
You can sense lunar energy?
Oh, look at that!
Wait, is that... guiding me?
I need to go this way.
What the fuck?
Hold up a second.
This is big.
We got to note it before we forget.
So this right here, overgrown cavern?
Yeah, it's definitely overgrown.
It's oversized as well.
It's way bigger than that.
It's like insanity.
Let me just, for now, do this.
There we go.
And then somewhere over here...
We have like a little...
There we go.
With another one of those... Oh, I can copy that shit.
Let's not redo that.
Here we go.
Copy that, baby.
And throw it over here.
What?
Where did it go?
Oh, there we go.
Also, the contents are different.
This is not in there.
Use this.
There we go.
What did it look like?
Moon with a radar on it.
So,
moon...
And we have some circles.
I'm trying to make this pretty as well.
Wait, what?
Fail to find latex stuff?
No, stop, stop!
Wrong button!
Here we go.
Ellipse, green, and make it a little thinner.
Oh, we can't do that.
There we go.
We're gonna put that on top.
Yeah, cool.
I like it.
Switch back.
Don't forget.
There we go.
All right, baby.
That's cool.
But I was about to dig to the right now, though.
Do I go... Oh, you know what?
The moon stuff is probably in the sky.
So, I'm probably gonna have to go up to the clouds again.
Oh, but I have teleport now.
Okay, we're gonna do that.
But first, I'm gonna make a path.
I'm just gonna dig right.
I don't give a shit.
We're going.
Kind of regret I didn't put speed on it now.
Now that I'm gonna dig again.
I think it would be quicker in the end, because I am pausing a lot when I walk here.
And especially, I could be teleporting through.
But fuck it.
I'm here now.
I don't want to go back.
Doesn't matter.
Make it more straight.
I'm sort of crooked.
You saw that?
When I click over here, sometimes there comes like a circle like that.
I'm trying to listen, too.
Oh!
Wait, am I okay if I...
I'm not letting this stop me.
Hold on.
If I make it big enough, sort of...
Oh, no!
Oh, but wait!
I keep healing!
Oh, dude!
This is...
What if I stand on it?
How fast do I lose HP?
Oh, it's really fast!
But if I keep spamming?
It's okay!
Oh, this feels wrong!
It feels really wrong.
But I'm going.
I'm doing it.
We're going!
We're fucking going!
Fuck it all!
This is nuts!
I have no idea where we're going.
But I like it.
Yo!
Okay!
The music.
Okay, that was just temporary.
I thought that was there, like, as a prevention of people to go outside of bounds, you know?
And I was, like, beating that prevention.
But okay!
Where do we end up?
I don't understand this green circle that pops up sometimes.
Fuck your cursed rock!
Water!
Wait a second.
What?
Where the fuck am I?
A huge reservoir of water.
East Lake!
Oh!
Cool!
Multiple lakes!
There's also one in the west.
You know what's funny?
This looks exactly like the place that I died when I had 1 HP, remember?
I was, like, I had the spell that would collapse rock, and one of the pieces fell straight on my head.
That's actually a cool memory.
Oh no, don't let water in here.
Yo, this is a big ass lake!
What the fuck?
Hold on.
Guys, I gotta take a quick piss.
I know it's kind of exciting right now.
Be right back.
Let's keep digging.
Dude, there's so much water.
Also, my tunnel down there is going to be flooded, by the way.
That tunnel is kind of ripped.
I'm just saying that.
So if I want to go back, I have to make another tunnel, I think.
But that's okay.
Wait.
You know, this game is so cool in that...
There's just...
So, the original...
I said this before, I'm going to say it again, but...
So the game is, like, layered vertically at first, right?
And nothing in the game hints at the fact that there may be other, like...
You know, like, stages.
You know, like, you have the hemisphere, you have the coal pits and all that.
But if you just go off-road, you end up finding cool little areas.
And here I found another fucking lake.
It's so cool.
I'm going to go all the way to the top.
Also, the more up we go, I guess...
Wait, we're actually getting quite far up.
I have teleport!
I completely forgot.
Holy shit, we got teleport!
I'm not used to it!
Dude, how tall is this?
What the fuck?
Oh!
The fuck is that?
Hello?
Oh shit!
Oh no!
Do we even want to be here?
This seems bad!
Fuck it!
We're taking a swim!
Whoa!
This is a massive drop!
Massive drop!
That's awesome!
Hopefully this guy doesn't follow me.
I mean, do I even care?
I can just keep healing, man!
This is so insane!
I can't die!
I mean, unless I polymorph, of course.
Dude, I wonder if there's a way to just not get polymorphed.
Because that is actually my only real scare at this point.
Because I can just heal through anything.
This is a big ass lake.
This shit is not fucking around.
East snowy wasteland.
The airfield is freezing.
What the fuck is...
This almost looked like my game is bugged in the same way when my game crashed and I had to restore, remember?
This doesn't look right.
What the fuck is going on?
Oh?
What's this?
What?
More?
There's more than four?
I don't know why I'm so surprised.
I guess I am because I thought the note we found was relating to these.
Okay.
Also, it's night again.
I am actually kind of missing my digging one that just goes...
where I can go like a worm.
Like, for situations like this.
The black hole is not always the thing I want, you know what I mean?
Dude, where the fuck am I actually right now?
What is that?
Huh?
This game just keeps going!
East frozen vault?
There's two of them?
Blow it all up.
I don't give a shit.
I don't discriminate east or west.
I blow shit up indiscriminately.
Oh, I guess I'll explore this for a bit.
I can just keep healing.
Oh, we got a wand.
Oh, look at that!
It was pulling up the explosive.
That's funny.
Okay, no thanks.
I actually kind of...
Dude, I'm so far away from home, I'm not going to be able to change my wands anytime soon.
It's actually kind of a bummer.
But, I do have teleport wands, so I can actually get back quick, I guess.
Whoops.
Oh, it's actually kind of dangerous because this sucks in those guys.
But, I am immune to explosions, so...
maybe I'm fine.
Hey, friendos!
How you doing?
This game is huge.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, calm down.
What the fuck?
Well, there are so many enemies.
Too bad they're not a match for me, huh?
This guy was stuck in the terrain.
That's fun.
I just love the gravitational effect that he just pulls up in everything.
It's a lot of fun.
Oh, what's that?
Null shot.
Increases a protectile's duration dramatically, but removes all damage and an explosion from it.
Yo!
That's a black hole modifier, if I've ever seen one.
And accelerating shot.
I feel like this wand is made for black holes.
Jesus.
And drilling?
I kind of want it.
Oh, but do I let go of damage plus?
You know what?
I don't need it.
I don't need it because I already have...
I can black hole forever, basically, and I can put speed on black holes.
I don't actually need this.
It's cool?
But let's be realistic here.
I don't really need it.
I don't understand where I am on my map right now.
This is very weird.
I'm just going to keep digging.
I started systematically digging, you know, left and right and all that, but at this point it's just like...
I feel like the game is so overwhelming with all the areas.
That at this point I'm just like, fuck it, we're going wherever.
It's so wild to me.
Look at that!
A flag in a hole.
Get black hole.
Bloop.
1376 HP.
I wonder if that is the most HP I've had.
I think I was over a thousand.
The last time I was over a thousand.
Obviously.
But you know what I mean.
I don't remember if I was over this.
That was the run where I had the perk that gave me 50 HP instead of 25.
Oh, here we go.
So, that makes sense.
There must be four of these as well, then.
Right?
Like, if there's four essences, we have four essence eaters.
So, now we need to find the fourth.
I'm assuming there's four.
Yo, this is large as hell!
Where the hell am I?
Hold on, this doesn't make any fucking sense.
Wait a minute.
So...
I...
I duck from here.
Right?
And...
I know there's a wall somewhere over here.
I guess I just duck through that.
I duck through a massive wall.
And now the surface just continues.
Weird.
Okay.
I actually don't have room on my map for that.
I need to...
I guess.
I also gotta measure how far up that goes.
That's a huge mountain.
I thought for sure that was the end when I first encountered that wall.
Oh, you motherfuckers.
Is he... Yeah, he's buffing them with... Yeah, okay.
Stop buffing them!
That's right.
Wait, East Ancient Laboratory?
I'm so confused!
Get this.
What do you mean, East Ancient Laboratory?
What the fuck is that?
Flammoxium in a giant...
Uh...
Crystal ball.
Or glass ball.
This shit is weird.
Guys?
What's going on down here?
Is this the East Coast?
East Coast represent?
Weird that it's called, like, East when the other is not called West.
No.
Please get the black hole out.
Thank you.
Hold on, I need to keep going here.
Oh, I've neutralized.
Not that it... Hold on.
Oh, I can't even heal with the neutralization on.
Everything is neutralized.
Can't do nothing.
This just keeps going.
This is so weird.
What?
Alright, it's party time, bitches.
Dance for me.
Huh.
We're bagging another wood.
Do we get another desert?
I am so far from home right now.
What?
Oh, I looped back around?
Oh, by the way, I just noticed.
You see this?
This right there is actually the same shit we saw when I...
when I used the demon eye.
And the fungal caverns.
Remember?
Look at that.
It's the exact same thing.
This is alluding to exactly that.
So does that mean if I bring this out?
That's actually kind of elegant.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
No, no, no, no.
Wait.
Where's the tree?
Wait, I'm so confused.
There's no tree.
Am
I fucking high right now?
Did I take too many shrooms?
What's happening?
There is... there's no tree.
Also, it's called east shit.
Yo.
Dude!
I know what's happening.
Remember the tablet that said everything has a counterpart?
Like dark matter.
Is it that?
Like the moon has a counterpart?
A dark moon?
Oh.
This is so weird.
Wait.
Wait a minute.
It's exactly the same.
What is that?
Oh.
An orb of corrupted knowledge.
What?
No.
Oh, no.
What did I do?
Oh, this is definitely the dark version of whatever the fuck was happening before.
I mean, I can keep healing.
That's the...
It stopped.
Wait.
Is it only out here?
Thank the fucking lord.
I thought I was gonna have to spam my heal and find some kind of essence eater for this.
Thank God.
So what the fuck is this?
East mines?
This is wild.
Huh?
They're not even that scary.
I was expecting at least like hard enemies here.
Thank you.
I'll take this.
I can't think straight, guys.
This is weird as fuck.
I don't even care about this.
I can heal.
I'm unstoppable.
Are the wands any better?
This is so weird.
Oh, yeah, I think they definitely do more damage.
The wand is shit.
Look at this.
Actually, it's not that bad.
I guess.
No, but this... Wait, do we...
What
the...
Wait, what?
I'm so confused.
So it is...
Also, wait, the moon is right above me.
I am not the same place.
Wait, what the fuck?
I'm so confused.
Huh?
How do I get... go back?
Wait, what happens if I go in here now?
Okay, I'm just back.
Okay, well...
Awesome!
I want to change my wand anyway.
Get rid of that.
Get rid of these.
Fucking awesome.
Look at this.
We're slapping this bad boy on here.
Oh, we run out of mana now, but...
Hmm.
I think it's worth it, maybe.
Let's see the damage.
Four, six... this...
Oh, wait, that actually doesn't do much.
It's not like... mind-blowingly good or anything.
Oh, that's not good.
Well, shit.
This is kinda... useless now.
I am so confused by what's happening in this game.
I can't tell you.
This is simply the weirdest...
thing that has happened to me in this game so far.
Is there anything else I want to do to my wand while I'm here?
I want to put speed on that.
No, not speed.
I want to put acceleration.
This one.
Yeah.
Because now we can teleport.
What else do I want to do?
Just order this normally.
This is fine now, right?
Yeah, we're good there.
Can we even put this in?
Is this too much?
Hold on, is that...
Is that worse?
I feel like it's worse.
Why is it worse, though?
Is it the Castile?
Wait.
It's .02 extra Castile.
There's no way that's the one.
Like, this should be better in all ways.
Wait, put it...
No, put it here.
Oh, we run out of mana quick like that.
Yeah, okay.
No, this is better.
It actually does also feel faster.
Yeah, listen.
Definitely faster.
Wow, such a small change in Castile can do so much.
That's incredible.
That one...
Okay, I have teleport.
I have this.
In fact, maybe I'll put...
this one on...
180.
No, I don't have mana for that on that.
Let's see.
Now that I have an extra wand free, what will I do?
What should I put on it?
I kind of want to put... I'm immune to explosions now.
So...
Oh, that's odd.
I've never seen that.
Look at this.
The way... Oh, that's cool.
Never noticed.
I was going to look for the holy hand grenade now because I am immune to that.
I think that would be fun.
Maybe have a...
Oh!
Maybe this one, the Nala, would be insane.
So imagine, we do a spark bolt, double trigger or a single trigger.
We put a hand grenade at the end with a Nala modifier on it so that I shoot it and right where impact, it goes... immediately.
If that is indeed how that works.
Maybe the Nala is not actually working that way.
But it could be cool.
Okay.
Alright, let's... Let me see this now.
Oh yeah, that's sick.
That's sick.
We can do some digging with that bad boy.
Okay.
Okay, so we got to map this now.
The playtime is over, bitch.
It's time to get serious.
We need to start our serious mapping expedition.
I'm going to go on the surface now.
And because I have teleport, it's going to be... Oh, I keep forgetting I have teleport.
Yeah, I have teleport.
So we're going to go back up here.
No, I don't give a fuck about that.
We go over here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Boink.
Shoot it.
And then we teleport through.
I could make my teleport one better, I guess.
It's a little... shit, isn't it?
It's okay.
Yeah, this could be better.
Ah, it's okay.
I can live with that.
This is miles faster than what we had before.
Oh yeah.
Oh, this is such a game changer.
We could put speed on the teleport as well and...
Oh, how about that spell that modifies the duration of it to be longer, but it doesn't do any damage and all that.
Remember that one?
Because I don't want the... and we don't... this is the only teleport we have.
I guess we could use a normal teleport and not a small one.
But we don't have that.
But this is totally fine.
This looks so silly by the way.
I'm just fucking teleporting through the world.
Not even touching the ground.
How different is this from the beginning, huh?
Hey!
Music me.
I wish the music would stay with you when you leave.
No, I can kick on a... okay, here we go.
So here's the wall and it's actually...
right next to... the machine.
So...
Wow, I actually did that pretty good, I guess.
Here's the wall.
How far up does it go?
I guess we already know the answer to that.
But we gotta map this.
I need to see all the way up now.
If I encounter obstacles up here, I just... like, hold through.
Oh, that's right!
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
This is... this is one of those...
Hold up, hold up, hold up.
That's right.
Yeah, we don't want that.
Nope.
Nope, we do not want that.
Let's mark this.
Fuck!
I'm sorry!
I swear, for next time, I'm gonna...
make something that will put something on my screen.
If I have the map open while I play, I promise.
Okay?
This technical issue is only for today.
I promise I'll fix that for next time.
I'm so sorry.
I'm gonna copy the pyramid down here.
Throw that bad boy up here.
And then...
inside of this...
Whoops.
Used this one.
There we go.
We had the essence of Earth.
Essence of Earth.
It's like a spell, I guess.
Nah, that's not... I'm not happy with that.
We're gonna zoom in.
Okay, can't zoom in anymore.
I'm just gonna do that.
That's the essence of Earth.
Essence of Earth.
Beautiful.
Mapped.
Hashtag mapped.
Change back.
There we go.
I'm so sorry for what I've put you guys through today.
Oh, man.
Wild.
Okay, so the...
Wait, what?
When did I do this?
Say what?
Oh, I know when I did it.
Just before, when I made a hole in the middle.
Yeah.
I did that.
It was me.
I'm guilty.
Now, what's up here?
We got a roof.
And it just sort of goes to the left.
How far to the... oh, goes to here.
If we want to be really precise, I could drop down right now and see where we are on the floor.
You know what?
Let's be really precise.
Oh, okay.
Right next to tower.
Lovely.
Now we go back up.
Back.
Up.
We go.
Oh, that wasn't that far up, actually.
Holy shit.
And... wow.
And then another... wow.
They were really hiding that place I was in, huh?
Holy crap.
Holy cannoli.
Okay.
Make it like a little jaggedy because it's rocky and all that, you know?
It goes like that.
How far does it go?
So let me make it straight.
Or actually just do... do this.
Draw like that.
There.
Then it goes up again.
Oh, we're going up.
And then at some point, it does that bullshit.
That's insane.
What?
So that means switch back.
Let me black hole my way up.
I gotta see this with my own damn eyes.
There is a top.
Okay, hold on.
Oh, what the hell?
This world is fucked up.
This is... so weird.
But it's so cool at the same time.
Bro, I'm going up.
We are going to the damn moon.
Wow.
Shit, shit, shit.
Don't fall, don't fall.
What is this?
Look at the background.
You know what?
I'm starting to believe you guys when you say that there are people that still haven't found all the secrets.
Or that the community still has secrets to find in this game.
I totally believe it.
This is... wild to me.
It just keeps going.
Am I going into space?
Look at the moon.
I'm soon at the same level.
I'm coming moon!
Oh, we're going up to the stars, baby.
Look at the background!
I'm at the same level.
I'm overtaking the moon.
Does this actually keep going?
Man, I'm glad I have teleport here, huh?
Good thing I didn't do this without the teleport.
Can you imagine that?
There has to be an end.
This... I feel like there's no end.
I'm way above the moon.
Okay, here's the plan.
I'm going to drop down until the moon is at my level.
And then I'm going to black hole my way through.
So it's exactly when it's at my level.
And...
Jesus.
Wait.
Hold it.
Steady.
There.
Ah, there we go.
Let's go.
Oh!
Wow.
That's it?
That's all that took?
Actually, we're quite a bit up.
We need to go a little more like this.
This is fucking crazy.
We may be here a while, guys.
I have no idea where this thing is.
Am I f- The work.
Wait, we've been in a place called The Work, haven't we?
Hold on.
It's- I'm actually falling down.
It needs to go higher.
It's made of cheese.
It's actually made of cheese!
I was joking about it.
And then I moused over and it said cheese.
What?
Can I eat it?
Okay.
So, okay.
The moon is made of cheese.
I wonder- Is this like an Easter egg or something?
I'm sorry moon.
There's gotta be something at the center.
No?
Oh!
Ooh, there's something.
Say what?
What does that say?
You know what?
I'm taking a picture of this with my phone.
There we go.
That looks like a note, doesn't it?
Like a musical note?
Maybe we need to play the sa- the moon a song?
S.G.P.
Something?
I don't know if I should read these as J and 0 or O's because that's definitely a gamma.
Oh, wait a minute.
You can sense lunar energy.
That's an integral sign.
No, that's- is that also a note?
That's gamma.
This looks like something- like this- you would write DF or something at the end of an integral too.
Like this is the integrant, F, if it's even an F.
But this looks kind of like a note to me.
Equals- or like it's zero.
The fuck does this mean?
Hold on.
Every- Hmm.
Everything has its counterpart.
Right?
Dark moon.
Anything else in here?
That is so weird.
Wait, is it upside down?
Hold on.
I'm trying to turn my head.
I have no idea what that means.
But I took a picture of it with my phone, so we got it.
We got it.
I'm going back to my mapping.
Back to the wall.
I do not feel like dropping down right now because most likely clouds and most likely crazy enemies.
This game looks so- if someone came in here and didn't know what this game was about and they saw this.
I gotta be honest, if I saw this right now, what I'm doing here, I'll be like, what the fuck is this shit?
I'm not going to lie.
I would think that looks like a shit game.
But it's not what it looks like.
It's not shit.
If you just joined, it's not shit.
It's good.
It just looks silly right now.
Oh man.
I feel like I need to get another beer.
Alright, we can drop here for a while.
I'm chilling.
Oh, yeah.
Today has been crazy.
And by the way, guys, no deaths today.
No death stream.
How crazy is that?
Man, I am dropping forever, huh?
Let's see if I can outrun it.
Oh, damn it.
I was about to do a black hole downwards and see if I could outrun the black hole.
Would be a fun test.
Right.
So I came from down there.
Let's go right now.
Let's see what's over here.
I'm not fucking climbing that.
I'm making a hole through.
Oh, this is a bigger one.
Oh!
Right.
Oh.
We're back to this.
Keep healing.
Oh, we're bleeding bad.
We're leaving a trail of blood.
But it doesn't matter.
We can heal forever.
It really doesn't matter.
Oh, we can teleport.
We made it.
Hey, guys!
Oh, shit.
Uh-oh.
You know what?
No.
Oh, you're not even that scary.
Hey, you're shit.
You're nothing.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, no.
All right.
Fuck you.
I'm not dealing with you.
East?
Oh, no.
I don't like that at all.
Emergency new path.
That is so weird.
What the fuck?
It's that guy again.
Oh.
Run.
Fucking hell.
Get out of there.
I'm not dealing with you.
Okay, we're back here now.
Fuck.
I forgot to change my teleport wand.
It should have been better.
I was thinking, was there something else I needed to do?
Ugh.
It does sound a little cursed.
This is definitely like the cursed version of whatever the fuck the starting area is.
Like, when you take the health, it's like you take damage for a while.
I'm so happy that didn't last indefinitely.
Holy shit.
I can't tell you how happy I am.
That didn't last forever.
Whoo.
It's night now here.
I wonder if this is going to start tracking a dark moon instead soon.
Maybe a moon made of blue cheese.
So this place is super weird.
There's no tree.
But the start looks exactly the same and there's...
stuff on the mountain as well and this thing.
Okay.
Don't take the portal this time.
In fact, we don't need to.
I'm just going to dig.
Dude, is there a holy mountain here?
Yo.
Are we going to get perks?
There's no way.
Don't get your hopes up.
Don't fucking...
Oh, thanks.
There's just a health sitting right there.
Don't take the portal.
Okay.
This is definitely East Culpitz.
Yeah.
It does look very similar.
Dude, my heart rate is in the fucking sky right now.
Oh my God.
What?
No way.
Wow.
This is crazy.
And there's refresher and everything.
Not that I need it.
What?
Oh man, I don't even know what to say.
I feel like I don't know anything about this game.
I feel like everything I've learned has been a lie.
What is happening?
What?
And when you take the portal, you go back to another place.
That is so weird.
How is this real?
I don't care about the terrain.
I just make black holes.
Can I just... again?
Oh wait, let's be careful here.
Maybe we are able to collapse the mountain here as well.
Let's not do that.
What?
Oh, right.
Okay.
I am overpowered!
Teleport bolt.
What's this?
Energy shield sector.
Oh, when I have...
What?
Oh, that actually costs mana too.
That's funny.
I am in complete disbelief about what's going on in this game, guys.
I can't lie.
This is...
It's completely overwhelming what's happening.
This is changing everything.
I'm just gonna...
I want to see how deep the rabbit hole goes.
I'm like Alice in fucking Adventureland.
The enemies are not even harder.
It's so weird.
This is crazy.
Like, I am unstoppable.
I have actually become a god.
Huh?
The flammable gas is just sitting there.
It's leaking from that pipe.
Whoa!
Why did I get pushed back like that?
My jaw hurts because it's been on the floor for the past 30 minutes.
I'm not even kidding.
Like, I have a weird contortion on my face.
That is not normally something my face is able to do.
Everything has been a lie.
Keep going down.
We're Alice in Adventureland.
I don't know what the English fucking saying is for that.
Alice in Wonderland.
Adventureland.
It's because in Denmark we say Alice in Adventureland.
Which means...
No wait, that actually means...
Not Adventureland, that means...
Fairytailland.
Yeah, I don't know what's wrong with me.
Oh my god.
Dude, we can still find ticket with ones everywhere!
There's a chance!
Hold on.
Go up here.
Where's the entrance?
I guess over here?
Oh, wait, wait.
Okay, guys.
Vampirism has dropped from number one.
It's no longer number one.
It's still up there, but it's not number one anymore.
Ticket with Wands is back on number one.
Uh, wait.
Whoa!
I didn't pay attention.
I must have hit something.
Teleportation.
Not
that it matters.
I mean, fuck everything, right?
Whoa, I don't even care!
Dude, not even these things!
Look, I give zero fucks.
The gods are angry, I don't care.
Oh, that's convenient that I'm here.
Hello.
I'm just happy that I have made peace with the gods.
I mean, I would probably murder them anywhere at this point, but still.
All seeing eye, that's perfect.
I would love that.
Earthquake.
Yo, that's also infinite, then.
I have to reorganize my brain.
Nothing is limited.
There's no limits.
Let's see the perks.
Stainless armor.
Homing shots.
I think it's time to re-roll.
No, actually, this is good.
I like that.
Okay, we need to find better wands.
We don't need this at all.
We're so powerful.
Take it.
Let's see the wand.
It's shuffle.
Doesn't matter, though.
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, yeah.
This is already better.
It's already better.
This also means if we don't, we can always, even if we...
Oh, dude, my whole brain is breaking right now.
All my strategies are changing right now for future runs.
Let me see this.
Oh, that's nuts.
Hold on.
Oh, my God, it's way better.
It's way better.
It's so good.
And you know what?
You know what?
Oh, dude, nothing is limited.
Look at this.
We're going to do that one and that one.
That should work, right?
When that reaches one or zero, I don't know why.
Sometimes it's one.
Other times it's zero.
I don't understand that part, but sure.
Fuck, yeah.
Oh, wait, it only lasts a little while.
Guys,
I can't wait for the post stream chat.
I just I can't wait to hear the talk with you guys about this.
This is...
Oh, no.
I was stuck in the snow.
I don't even know what I'm doing.
I'm just sort of in disbelief still.
Just go down.
Yeah.
What's that?
Acceleration.
You know what?
I will chock that.
Chock the acceleration.
Maximum speed.
Well, almost fell in.
I do wonder if this will also take me back to the other place.
I don't want to risk it, though.
It came all the way here.
Wait, wait, wait.
We've chocked it.
Throw it.
Grab this.
We're back.
Get down the hole.
Oh, almost broke that.
Let's be careful here.
Oh, here we go.
I get, I get whole new perks.
Two, no.
We do not want to do that.
Two random perks.
That could ruin everything.
Imagine if we got the perk.
Can't change or like it at once anywhere.
That would be bad.
I do wonder if this one, extra item in Holy Mountain works retroactively.
Oh, you haven't discovered yet.
Never mind.
The answer was right there.
Reroll.
Wand radar.
Exploding gold.
Summon city kiwi.
Gain an artifact that allows you to call the celestial rage.
You know what?
I don't like any of these.
Let's just try it.
This run is insane anyway.
Let's just go nuts.
Put this here for now.
Careful.
Gonna turn off.
It's gonna turn off.
Or not.
This artifact has a picture of a celestial beam.
How's it work?
Oh, I right click it?
Maybe.
No.
Do I shoot it?
Oh, maybe I kick it actually.
Oh!
You feel like you should move?
Oh, whoa!
What?
Wait, where's the being?
Holy...
Whoa!
Wait.
No.
It made a hole through the damn world!
Can I do it?
Oh, it's one off.
Oh, that was cool as hell!
I mean...
Whatever.
I mean, I don't really...
Now I kind of regret getting it, I guess.
But no, not really.
Because it was cool to figure out what it did, I guess.
That's awesome!
The gods have been looking away for quite a while now.
Man, the shit they put up with, huh?
Damn, I have been a real nuisance to these gods.
God damn.
Uplicate spell.
What is that?
Hold on.
Get away from me.
Also, I have melee immunity as well, I just...
I am fucking on cloud nine right now.
Uh...
Cast a copy of a projectile in a bifurcated pattern, but the copy still costs...
mana.
Wait, does this work with...
It says copy!
No, it doesn't.
The copy still...
Hmm.
Maybe because it costs mana?
Okay, it doesn't work like that.
Uh...
Just checking.
It does say copy though, so now I am confused why this one works at all.
Cast copies of every spell...
It must be...
Maybe because this is a type other, and that's just what that does?
As a type?
Whereas this is a utility?
Hmm.
Whatever.
Yeah, that's still working fine.
Alright.
Well, I had to try.
Uh...
Also, the prices here are the same price as they would be in this stage of the game.
What's this?
Poison Trail?
What's happening across rain cloud?
Damn.
Damn!
Wow.
Just insane.
And now we're in the jungle!
Now we're in the jungle.
Whoops.
Oh.
Like, I'm just murdering everything.
East Fungal Caverns.
Heh.
Wait a minute, is there a west as well?
Wait.
Dude!
West?
Non-wester east and east?
We gotta try that at some point.
It's gotta be.
Why would it be called east?
I feel like I can't handle any more craziness.
This...
Oh, shit.
I'm teleporting.
Wait.
I'm in the...
Oh, I'm in the Fungal Caverns now.
Oh, but wait!
Let's try this here now.
No, wait.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
That was in the cold pits.
I'm losing my mind.
I don't even know where I am right now.
All the zones are flowing together for me.
It's, it's, yeah.
Yeah.
I'm completely losing my mind here.
A bunch of chainsaws.
I think I would like that.
Hold on.
I'll be back for you.
Don't go anywhere.
No.
Oh, wait.
I'm immune.
They don't do any damage to me.
Shit.
Yeah, just, just...
Can I do...
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Why don't I just do that?
Oh.
Isn't that just straight up better?
It's more damage?
It doesn't dig though, but I don't care about that really.
I can dig in with other ways.
In fact, even better.
We quadruple this motherfucker.
Oh.
Oh my God.
Holy shit.
Why is it...
Oh, this one costs five mana.
That's why.
Do I need this?
I need that.
Unless...
Unless we do some kind of shenanigans here.
Trigger, quadruple one, two, three, and then it casts one more.
Double dipping?
Can we do a double dip somehow?
What are we limited by?
Castelay for sure.
Oh, this only reduces recharge time, of course.
Yeah.
But that makes so much...
That's like approximately 0.6, like 0.5.
This is recharge time of zero now.
It's minus castelay plus...
So these cancel almost?
Crit chance?
This adds a little castelay.
This reduces recharge.
Hmm.
Okay, I'm not quite sure what's going on, but let's just leave it like that for now.
Maybe we don't need this many.
Can we do with a triple instead?
Do I have a triple?
Fuck.
Maybe I do.
Hmm.
What's that again?
Circle of oil.
I'm still trying to make peace with the fact that all this crazy shit is happening in the game.
It's...
Man.
I'm tempted...
Don't do it.
Bad idea.
We'll only get hurt.
Maybe called Drupal, we wait with that.
Just put the...
This one.
Oh wait, unless we can find a...
Hold on.
What does that look like?
Well, that's not bad.
What's the damage like?
Makes it a bit slower actually.
Oh, because of this.
That's really solid.
That's really good.
These two together...
I think it's really good.
That's cool.
We add that at the...
End.
Why is that not...
It's not working.
Oh, it's the wrong one.
I'm an idiot.
There we go.
Heh heh.
Now we do run out of mana, but...
I do kind of like this double shield.
I think that's really cool.
Let's keep this.
Skip that there.
Let's put that there.
I want all these chainsaws.
And...
Maybe we get rid of that one.
And we add this one.
Hold on.
What is this one again?
I don't think I like this.
Leave it here.
Then put...
That one in there in case we need it later.
That's cool.
I like that.
Yep.
Oh, wait!
Triple, triple, triple!
We have a triple!
That's what I was looking for!
Oh yeah!
There we go!
Fuck yeah!
Cool, good thing I just spotted that.
Alright!
Throw it away.
Boing!
Let's go.
What's that?
Oh, I killed something I guess.
Dude, I'm immune to spiders now!
I don't give a fuck about anything!
This is just insane.
It's weird how it stops here and doesn't like...
go all the way through.
Let's see the perks.
What's that?
A circle of water.
A circle of water?
Save what?
Oh, that's badass!
That's really cool looking!
Lovely!
Oh, now we're sort of flooded here.
Protect...
Protect how spells have a chance to duplicate.
But you're more vulnerable now.
You gain double the gold per nakis?
Maybe that ain't such a crazy idea!
Living on the edge.
Oh, your spells deal three times damage when you're under 25 HP.
Or 25% of maximum health.
Oh!
But I'm never going to be that because I heal insane.
Maybe this will be worth it so we can re-roll.
I feel like I'm so greedy right now.
A random always cast spell is added to the wand in your hand.
Oh man.
No.
I think...
this may be best.
I'm going greed!
We're greedy as fuck!
Okay, down.
I have to
remember, I don't have infinite spam on this.
I need to...
Oh man, I do so good damage.
The damage is so good.
Still...
Whoa!
Still haven't found an ad mana though.
Oh man, the black holes just destroy everything!
If I just smell where there's electricity, I shoot a black hole in that general direction and it's gone.
This is... this is not Noita anymore.
This is something else.
And I like it.
No, I mean I like both but...
Oh man.
The game has changed.
Completely changed.
Also the game hasn't crashed at all and I've been doing all kinds of crazy shit today.
It makes me happy.
Look, I'm just breezing through this.
I'm going straight down.
What do
we have here?
Oh, they're starting to cost a lot of money now.
Let's see, what's that?
Peplicate spell.
Oh, I really want to buy it and test it but...
not really.
Trick blood money.
Extra knockback.
I don't like any of these.
Maybe that one.
You know what's good about this one?
Let's say for example...
that...
I discover something cool.
For example, the chest that we couldn't open.
I think I can pick that up with that and bring it back home.
So I can experiment on it at home.
You know, stuff like that.
Yeah.
Guys, I'm overwhelmed.
Well, this is almost 10 hours stream.
I need to stop here.
This is fucking crazy what's going on.
I don't have no words.
I need to eat.
I need to collect my thoughts.
I need to calm down.
Because that was insane.
What a run!
And it's not over!
And no deaths?
Didn't even have to update the death counter today.
What do you say to them apples?
Huh?
Hold on, I'm going to put on some noise and music.
If I can find some.
Or no, we need something fitting here.
Something atmospheric.
I'm going to put on some Talos principle.
I think it's fitting.
Oh, man.
This was crazy.
Let me see what you guys are saying.
I'm going to pull up chat here.
What an amazing stream full of roller coasters for chat with the Greek letters.
And the Greek letters are insanely broken.
If I was playing this game alone, I think I would have Googled if that was a bug or not.
Because I was so convinced that I somehow did something that wasn't supposed to happen.
You did things not meant to be done and seen things not meant to be seen.
Now we are in the big time mode.
Fuck yeah, Garmon.
What do you think of your first venture into redacted worlds?
Dude, I am at a loss for words.
I have no... I don't know what to think yet.
I need to think about it.
But I guess my reaction to everything is an answer enough in itself, isn't it?
Do you like your first God run?
I love it!
I'm finally owning.
Except I'm going to get polymorph very soon.
Everything's going to be over.
The Greek letters and the East shit, huh?
Yeah.
Congrats on getting Greek spells finally.
We're all waiting for that.
Now the real game starts.
Also insane healing discovery.
That's right.
I discovered the whole jumping up into the thing.
Multicast on spark trigger.
I feel like I've just... I knew about that one before though.
That's not something I discovered today.
But okay.
Lots of new areas crossing into East world.
Insane no style stream.
Yeah.
My curiosity was indeed rewarded.
Greek letters are the real game changer.
It's so crazy though.
Like they really are.
It's like they went from the game was like, ah, you know, you get three black holes.
Like, oh, you want, you want infinite black holes here?
Like what a, what a jump.
Very jarring in a way too.
People were fucking kicking and screaming at you in chat to experiment with the Greek letter spells.
Dude, but I found them.
I didn't notice that they said copy and stuff.
I thought it was exactly like the other ones I had, you know, instead of it being random, it was just like, oh, you can do the first spell.
Tutorial is over.
We were so scared you would not figure out the letters.
Here's the thing.
There's going to be things I won't ever discover and that's okay.
And I don't mind.
It's totally fine.
You might want to have like a run specific map where you mark things that you wanted to remember.
Yeah.
I actually used to write run specific notes.
I think I'm going to do that for this as well.
I am definitely going to look at the VOD of today just to remind myself the exact layout.
There are certain things I still haven't filled out on the map that I want to fill out.
For example, the one where I kept going up forever and nothing happened and I had to go through stuff like that.
And also fix the proportions of things because some things are too close together and stuff.
I'm going to fix that up.
How do you feel about completing tutorial?
I feel like the tutorial was amazing.
If that was the tutorial, I'm amazed.
I think you're kidding though, but yeah.
The place with a lot of wands is called Wandmart in the community.
That's a great name.
Wandmart?
Oh, that's hilarious.
Wandmart!
That's the best!
Fucking... Dude, that's awesome.
You should name it that on your map.
I should!
Oh, man.
How did the moon cheese taste like Oliver?
Very good, but because I was also very hungry.
Like I ate a sandwich halfway through the stream, but I am dying right now again because this was a long ass dream.
I was not expecting to stream this long, but it was just so exciting.
I never died.
I kept finding new things.
Fucking addicting!
For real.
Very few spells in this game are useless.
Yeah, I imagine so.
I absolutely love the stream.
Hey, EMDMeister.
You were so goddamn smart about many things.
Can't wait for you to solve all the mysteries of Noita.
The game has so much potential and room for it.
Great run.
Thank you, man.
I appreciate it.
Thanks for joining and watching.
I have to say it again.
Your enthusiasm is so entertaining.
Man, the game is so entertaining.
How can you not be enthused?
But thank you.
I'm glad you're enjoying it.
How many hours of playtime now?
Let me check.
119.4 hours.
119.4.
At least on Steam.
I was kidding about the tutorial.
This is the makings of a true God run.
What do you mean the makings?
This is a God run so far.
Until it isn't.
Until I die.
You forgot the crackers to your cheese, though, Oliver.
You gotta go back.
Oh, man.
I feel like getting crackers and cheese now.
I should totally relax with that later.
It was fun that you said it's made of cheese just before it said it.
It was yellow!
Right?
And that's a common thing to say about the moon.
When you were going to the moon, I jumped into my own God run to rush to find the moon first.
Oh, you hadn't seen it before.
And on the way there, I just heard, it's actually made of cheese!
That's amazing, Ujiri.
I love that.
I'm just imagining us racing to the moon.
You're like, come on, I gotta get there first.
And then you just hear that out of the blue.
That's amazing.
Total fever dream stream.
I know.
I actually, I'm not kidding.
I did feel like I was, it was an out of body experience today.
You know how you're so into a game?
Time doesn't even exist anymore.
That's how I felt.
Man, this music right here makes me want to get into the Talos Principle 2.
I've been waiting for that game, man.
Just listen to this fucking soundtrack.
How is that not a masterpiece, huh?
Oh yeah, it's so fitting as well.
You know what's so fitting about this?
I found Greek letters.
And this game takes place in a, or takes place in an area similar to Greece.
You know?
It's perfect.
Mr. Beat, I didn't read your text or your message because I think it may be a spoiler.
So I stopped reading it.
Don't spoil anything, please.
If you were spoiling, maybe you were joking.
I don't know.
Have you decided what you're going to do after Pray Oliver?
Not yet.
Oh, you made a joke.
Okay, okay.
Excuse me, do you have a moment to talk about your course extended party?
If I was a developer, I would have put that in.
Somehow.
That would have been so funny.
That's a good one.
Nice.
Okay, they're just joking.
Yeah, yeah.
Dude, Neuter is awesome.
What a game.
The meat realm.
That's right.
I discovered that too.
I did so much today.
I killed my worst nemesis.
In fact, I mopped the floor with them.
I found the meat realm.
I dug and found all kinds of things.
I mapped out whole new areas.
I made amazing drawings of in-game drawings in my own drawing.
I was an artist today.
I was a quiet man, an artist.
And I did things.
It's a really good game for its price.
Damn right.
I even got it on a discount.
I kind of feel bad.
Like, what a game.
And the room with the pot in.
Yeah, that's true.
Good thing you're making a map because otherwise you would miss some hidden areas for sure.
Like, I could tell even earlier before I started making the map that maybe I should make a map.
Because I was getting lost so easily.
Especially the first times I went west and I discovered the whole snow area.
And the big lake and all that.
I just knew I had to make a map.
I feel like I've been suffering a lot and dying stupid deaths.
But today it's all being redeemed, you know?
The knowledge has reached the level where I'm able to do things like this.
I was afraid the alchemist despawned, but he somehow came back.
Yeah.
I thought so too.
Because he did that the first time.
At least I think so.
Thought you said I was an artist today?
No, I mean, I was trying not to say artist, but in like a British voice.
So I was like, artist.
Probably that's a terrible British voice.
Music is getting demonic.
Wait, is it fucked?
What about my voice?
Is it back?
Is it good?
Oh, it got crispy.
I think it's because I'm using a browser source to get the audio.
It's okay now.
I do have some audio issues from time to time.
Also, thanks.
Thank you, meeps kitten for six months, man.
At tier one.
Thank you so much.
Illuminati also and a lady again gave out three community gifts or subs.
I really appreciate that.
Oh, I can see you made a prediction.
Will we kill the alchemist?
I want to know.
Who bet the most on that one?
Who put their potatoes on the line?
Vacuum cleaner.
I love your name.
You just called vacuum cleaner.
Welcome.
Lovely.
I remember back when people were excited that you're discovering that you could edit once.
I mean, that is a big deal, right?
Discovering that is a big deal.
The knowledge you gain in this game is definitely layered like that.
Man, I'm so happy.
Okay, guys, it's time for me to bounce on out of here and get some food.
I have approximately 12 minutes before the stores close.
So I'm going to hurry really quick.
I'm going to send you over and we're going to raid someone.
Okay?
From the same category.
Don't go anywhere.
Same category.
Let's see who's streaming.
Oh, we've got fury forged.
We got us.
We got to raid him.
He says sparks are flying flask alchemy.
Let's let's check that out, guys.
I'm going to go to the store.
I'll see you guys around.
Thank you so much for watching and subscribing.
You're the best.
I'll see you next time.
Good night.
Thank you.